{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588735183","data":{"timestamp":" 947588735182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588736679","data":{"timestamp":" 947588736679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588750755","data":{"timestamp":" 947588750755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588752864","data":{"timestamp":" 947588752864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588754804","data":{"timestamp":" 947588754804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588757282","data":{"timestamp":" 947588757282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588760263","data":{"timestamp":" 947588760263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588761925","data":{"timestamp":" 947588761924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588765470","data":{"timestamp":" 947588765469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588769546","data":{"timestamp":" 947588769546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588772825","data":{"timestamp":" 947588772824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" START_MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588773984","data":{"timestamp":" 947588773984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588775703","data":{"timestamp":" 947588775702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588777758","data":{"timestamp":" 947588777757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588783082","data":{"timestamp":" 947588783082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588784476","data":{"timestamp":" 947588784475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" START_MARIDADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588786452","data":{"timestamp":" 947588786452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588788179","data":{"timestamp":" 947588788178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588789360","data":{"timestamp":" 947588789359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588790264","data":{"timestamp":" 947588790263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588791354","data":{"timestamp":" 947588791353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588792376","data":{"timestamp":" 947588792375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588793247","data":{"timestamp":" 947588793246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588794358","data":{"timestamp":" 947588794358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588795039","data":{"timestamp":" 947588795037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588796341","data":{"timestamp":" 947588796340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588798736","data":{"timestamp":" 947588798736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588800548","data":{"timestamp":" 947588800548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588801946","data":{"timestamp":" 947588801946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" START_KUMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588803701","data":{"timestamp":" 947588803700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588805101","data":{"timestamp":" 947588805101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588806063","data":{"timestamp":" 947588806063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588807053","data":{"timestamp":" 947588807053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588808880","data":{"timestamp":" 947588808879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588810663","data":{"timestamp":" 947588810663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588810675","data":{"timestamp":" 947588810674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588811067","data":{"timestamp":" 947588811067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588811821","data":{"timestamp":" 947588811821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588813302","data":{"timestamp":" 947588813302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588814743","data":{"timestamp":" 947588814742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588816380","data":{"timestamp":" 947588816380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588817883","data":{"timestamp":" 947588817883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588819496","data":{"timestamp":" 947588819495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588819979","data":{"timestamp":" 947588819979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588821982","data":{"timestamp":" 947588821982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588822179","data":{"timestamp":" 947588822178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588823156","data":{"timestamp":" 947588823155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588824535","data":{"timestamp":" 947588824534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588824693","data":{"timestamp":" 947588824692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588825848","data":{"timestamp":" 947588825848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588826508","data":{"timestamp":" 947588826508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588827611","data":{"timestamp":" 947588827610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588828412","data":{"timestamp":" 947588828411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588828527","data":{"timestamp":" 947588828527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588829227","data":{"timestamp":" 947588829226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588832456","data":{"timestamp":" 947588832456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588833921","data":{"timestamp":" 947588833921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588834902","data":{"timestamp":" 947588834901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588835172","data":{"timestamp":" 947588835172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588836411","data":{"timestamp":" 947588836410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588837824","data":{"timestamp":" 947588837823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588839215","data":{"timestamp":" 947588839215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588840121","data":{"timestamp":" 947588840121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588842246","data":{"timestamp":" 947588842245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588843579","data":{"timestamp":" 947588843579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588845293","data":{"timestamp":" 947588845292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588848612","data":{"timestamp":" 947588848612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588850630","data":{"timestamp":" 947588850629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588851923","data":{"timestamp":" 947588851923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588853107","data":{"timestamp":" 947588853107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" START_CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588854143","data":{"timestamp":" 947588854143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588856085","data":{"timestamp":" 947588856084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588856757","data":{"timestamp":" 947588856756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588857954","data":{"timestamp":" 947588857953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588858830","data":{"timestamp":" 947588858829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588859065","data":{"timestamp":" 947588859064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588859694","data":{"timestamp":" 947588859693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588859812","data":{"timestamp":" 947588859812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588860823","data":{"timestamp":" 947588860823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588861733","data":{"timestamp":" 947588861733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588862432","data":{"timestamp":" 947588862431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888570","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888586","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888602","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888613","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888628","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888637","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888641","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888646","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588888652","data":{"timestamp":" 947588888652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588906620","data":{"timestamp":" 947588906619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588913478","data":{"timestamp":" 947588913477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588915547","data":{"timestamp":" 947588915547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588916589","data":{"timestamp":" 947588916588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588916794","data":{"timestamp":" 947588916793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588917497","data":{"timestamp":" 947588917497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588918510","data":{"timestamp":" 947588918509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588919503","data":{"timestamp":" 947588919503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588920253","data":{"timestamp":" 947588920252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588920852","data":{"timestamp":" 947588920851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588921712","data":{"timestamp":" 947588921711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588922230","data":{"timestamp":" 947588922229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588923080","data":{"timestamp":" 947588923079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588927103","data":{"timestamp":" 947588927103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588927810","data":{"timestamp":" 947588927810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588928869","data":{"timestamp":" 947588928869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588930288","data":{"timestamp":" 947588930287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588932089","data":{"timestamp":" 947588932089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588933276","data":{"timestamp":" 947588933276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588934786","data":{"timestamp":" 947588934786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588937772","data":{"timestamp":" 947588937771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588938889","data":{"timestamp":" 947588938889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588940660","data":{"timestamp":" 947588940660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588941746","data":{"timestamp":" 947588941746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" START_ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588943439","data":{"timestamp":" 947588943438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588945215","data":{"timestamp":" 947588945214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588946587","data":{"timestamp":" 947588946587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588952603","data":{"timestamp":" 947588952602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588954184","data":{"timestamp":" 947588954183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588955157","data":{"timestamp":" 947588955157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588956563","data":{"timestamp":" 947588956563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588960356","data":{"timestamp":" 947588960356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588965320","data":{"timestamp":" 947588965319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588966969","data":{"timestamp":" 947588966969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588971135","data":{"timestamp":" 947588971135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588974396","data":{"timestamp":" 947588974396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588977140","data":{"timestamp":" 947588977140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588980949","data":{"timestamp":" 947588980949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588993411","data":{"timestamp":" 947588993411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588995367","data":{"timestamp":" 947588995367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588997721","data":{"timestamp":" 947588997720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588998417","data":{"timestamp":" 947588998416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947588999218","data":{"timestamp":" 947588999218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589000365","data":{"timestamp":" 947589000364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589001023","data":{"timestamp":" 947589001022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589001683","data":{"timestamp":" 947589001682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589002393","data":{"timestamp":" 947589002392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589003326","data":{"timestamp":" 947589003325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589004220","data":{"timestamp":" 947589004219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589004469","data":{"timestamp":" 947589004468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589005754","data":{"timestamp":" 947589005754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589006340","data":{"timestamp":" 947589006339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589010650","data":{"timestamp":" 947589010650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589014081","data":{"timestamp":" 947589014081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589016124","data":{"timestamp":" 947589016123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589017936","data":{"timestamp":" 947589017935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589019073","data":{"timestamp":" 947589019073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589019200","data":{"timestamp":" 947589019200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589020051","data":{"timestamp":" 947589020050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589022074","data":{"timestamp":" 947589022073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589022418","data":{"timestamp":" 947589022417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589023166","data":{"timestamp":" 947589023166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589024827","data":{"timestamp":" 947589024827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589025319","data":{"timestamp":" 947589025318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589025835","data":{"timestamp":" 947589025835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589026333","data":{"timestamp":" 947589026332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589028876","data":{"timestamp":" 947589028876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589032260","data":{"timestamp":" 947589032259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589035427","data":{"timestamp":" 947589035427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589036560","data":{"timestamp":" 947589036560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589037588","data":{"timestamp":" 947589037588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" START_HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589039220","data":{"timestamp":" 947589039219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589041213","data":{"timestamp":" 947589041212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589041368","data":{"timestamp":" 947589041368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589043896","data":{"timestamp":" 947589043895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589045583","data":{"timestamp":" 947589045583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589047683","data":{"timestamp":" 947589047683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" START_KWAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589050877","data":{"timestamp":" 947589050877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589052311","data":{"timestamp":" 947589052310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589053462","data":{"timestamp":" 947589053462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589054855","data":{"timestamp":" 947589054854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589055525","data":{"timestamp":" 947589055524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589055984","data":{"timestamp":" 947589055983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589056604","data":{"timestamp":" 947589056604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589056981","data":{"timestamp":" 947589056980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589057192","data":{"timestamp":" 947589057191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589057619","data":{"timestamp":" 947589057618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589057668","data":{"timestamp":" 947589057668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589066106","data":{"timestamp":" 947589066106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589067804","data":{"timestamp":" 947589067803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" START_UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589069427","data":{"timestamp":" 947589069426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589070324","data":{"timestamp":" 947589070324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589072323","data":{"timestamp":" 947589072323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589073139","data":{"timestamp":" 947589073138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589075920","data":{"timestamp":" 947589075920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589077480","data":{"timestamp":" 947589077479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589078583","data":{"timestamp":" 947589078582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589083705","data":{"timestamp":" 947589083705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589085045","data":{"timestamp":" 947589085045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589086230","data":{"timestamp":" 947589086230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589087627","data":{"timestamp":" 947589087626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589088793","data":{"timestamp":" 947589088793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589089732","data":{"timestamp":" 947589089731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589091116","data":{"timestamp":" 947589091116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589092447","data":{"timestamp":" 947589092447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589092993","data":{"timestamp":" 947589092992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589094658","data":{"timestamp":" 947589094658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589096068","data":{"timestamp":" 947589096068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589097411","data":{"timestamp":" 947589097410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589099504","data":{"timestamp":" 947589099504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589101438","data":{"timestamp":" 947589101438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589102437","data":{"timestamp":" 947589102436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589103450","data":{"timestamp":" 947589103449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589103975","data":{"timestamp":" 947589103975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589104153","data":{"timestamp":" 947589104153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589105394","data":{"timestamp":" 947589105393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589106811","data":{"timestamp":" 947589106811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589107069","data":{"timestamp":" 947589107069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589108212","data":{"timestamp":" 947589108211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589108791","data":{"timestamp":" 947589108790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589114022","data":{"timestamp":" 947589114021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589116298","data":{"timestamp":" 947589116298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589117763","data":{"timestamp":" 947589117762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589119559","data":{"timestamp":" 947589119558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589121421","data":{"timestamp":" 947589121421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589123639","data":{"timestamp":" 947589123638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589125183","data":{"timestamp":" 947589125182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589127030","data":{"timestamp":" 947589127029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589127999","data":{"timestamp":" 947589127998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589128737","data":{"timestamp":" 947589128736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589129648","data":{"timestamp":" 947589129647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alikuwa mtoto mwerevu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589132555","data":{"timestamp":" 947589132554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALIWEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589134859","data":{"timestamp":" 947589134858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589137358","data":{"timestamp":" 947589137358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589137447","data":{"timestamp":" 947589137447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589138886","data":{"timestamp":" 947589138886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589147727","data":{"timestamp":" 947589147727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589149939","data":{"timestamp":" 947589149939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589152030","data":{"timestamp":" 947589152030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589153000","data":{"timestamp":" 947589153000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589154204","data":{"timestamp":" 947589154204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589155536","data":{"timestamp":" 947589155536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589157509","data":{"timestamp":" 947589157509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589159674","data":{"timestamp":" 947589159673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589160442","data":{"timestamp":" 947589160441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589161141","data":{"timestamp":" 947589161140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589161869","data":{"timestamp":" 947589161868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589162127","data":{"timestamp":" 947589162126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589162866","data":{"timestamp":" 947589162865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589164263","data":{"timestamp":" 947589164262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweza kujua mahali kisima cha karibu kilikokuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589168599","data":{"timestamp":" 947589168599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589168923","data":{"timestamp":" 947589168922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589170719","data":{"timestamp":" 947589170718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589172411","data":{"timestamp":" 947589172411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589173209","data":{"timestamp":" 947589173209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589174512","data":{"timestamp":" 947589174511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" BAHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589175725","data":{"timestamp":" 947589175725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589177475","data":{"timestamp":" 947589177475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589178095","data":{"timestamp":" 947589178094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589178966","data":{"timestamp":" 947589178964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589179781","data":{"timestamp":" 947589179781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589180008","data":{"timestamp":" 947589180007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589180658","data":{"timestamp":" 947589180658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" BAHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589181105","data":{"timestamp":" 947589181105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589184668","data":{"timestamp":" 947589184668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589189294","data":{"timestamp":" 947589189294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589191790","data":{"timestamp":" 947589191789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589193819","data":{"timestamp":" 947589193818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" START_KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589194595","data":{"timestamp":" 947589194594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589195614","data":{"timestamp":" 947589195614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589196117","data":{"timestamp":" 947589196117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589199043","data":{"timestamp":" 947589199043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589199046","data":{"timestamp":" 947589199046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589199770","data":{"timestamp":" 947589199770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589201430","data":{"timestamp":" 947589201430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589203177","data":{"timestamp":" 947589203176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589203740","data":{"timestamp":" 947589203740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589204669","data":{"timestamp":" 947589204669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589206202","data":{"timestamp":" 947589206201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589208092","data":{"timestamp":" 947589208092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589208841","data":{"timestamp":" 947589208840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589210579","data":{"timestamp":" 947589210579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589211258","data":{"timestamp":" 947589211258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589215176","data":{"timestamp":" 947589215176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589216743","data":{"timestamp":" 947589216743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589219017","data":{"timestamp":" 947589219017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589219845","data":{"timestamp":" 947589219844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589220362","data":{"timestamp":" 947589220361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589220624","data":{"timestamp":" 947589220624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589221351","data":{"timestamp":" 947589221350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589221597","data":{"timestamp":" 947589221596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589222807","data":{"timestamp":" 947589222807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589223610","data":{"timestamp":" 947589223608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589224485","data":{"timestamp":" 947589224483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589224993","data":{"timestamp":" 947589224992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka nyumbani kwenda kwa manyatta ya nyanyake lakini hakufika huko."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKO"," userResponse":" HUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589228593","data":{"timestamp":" 947589228593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589229309","data":{"timestamp":" 947589229308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589231329","data":{"timestamp":" 947589231328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589232225","data":{"timestamp":" 947589232225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589233660","data":{"timestamp":" 947589233660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589236241","data":{"timestamp":" 947589236241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTELEA"," userResponse":" ALIPOTELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589237427","data":{"timestamp":" 947589237427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipotelea milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589239768","data":{"timestamp":" 947589239768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589240872","data":{"timestamp":" 947589240872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589242579","data":{"timestamp":" 947589242579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589245809","data":{"timestamp":" 947589245809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589247653","data":{"timestamp":" 947589247653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589249506","data":{"timestamp":" 947589249505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589251053","data":{"timestamp":" 947589251053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589256553","data":{"timestamp":" 947589256553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589256557","data":{"timestamp":" 947589256556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589258740","data":{"timestamp":" 947589258739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589260322","data":{"timestamp":" 947589260322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589261345","data":{"timestamp":" 947589261345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589262307","data":{"timestamp":" 947589262306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EDOME"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589264674","data":{"timestamp":" 947589264674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" START_KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589266108","data":{"timestamp":" 947589266107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589267131","data":{"timestamp":" 947589267130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589268199","data":{"timestamp":" 947589268198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589270281","data":{"timestamp":" 947589270281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589270859","data":{"timestamp":" 947589270859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589270989","data":{"timestamp":" 947589270989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589271435","data":{"timestamp":" 947589271434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589271679","data":{"timestamp":" 947589271678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589272419","data":{"timestamp":" 947589272418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EDOME"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589273753","data":{"timestamp":" 947589273752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589274924","data":{"timestamp":" 947589274924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi chini ya mti wa edome kusubiri usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589278429","data":{"timestamp":" 947589278429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589279103","data":{"timestamp":" 947589279103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589280733","data":{"timestamp":" 947589280732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" KUOTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589282371","data":{"timestamp":" 947589282371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589284011","data":{"timestamp":" 947589284010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589285813","data":{"timestamp":" 947589285812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589286853","data":{"timestamp":" 947589286852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" EDOME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589288656","data":{"timestamp":" 947589288655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589291027","data":{"timestamp":" 947589291027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589291116","data":{"timestamp":" 947589291116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589291663","data":{"timestamp":" 947589291663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOTA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589292483","data":{"timestamp":" 947589292483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOTA"," userResponse":" KUOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589294048","data":{"timestamp":" 947589294048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589295519","data":{"timestamp":" 947589295518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589297167","data":{"timestamp":" 947589297166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589297815","data":{"timestamp":" 947589297814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589298851","data":{"timestamp":" 947589298850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589300040","data":{"timestamp":" 947589300039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589300275","data":{"timestamp":" 947589300274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589301064","data":{"timestamp":" 947589301063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOTA"," userResponse":" KUOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589301705","data":{"timestamp":" 947589301704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye alilala na kuota ndoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589305976","data":{"timestamp":" 947589305976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589306722","data":{"timestamp":" 947589306721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589308972","data":{"timestamp":" 947589308971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589309973","data":{"timestamp":" 947589309973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589311116","data":{"timestamp":" 947589311116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589312410","data":{"timestamp":" 947589312410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589313307","data":{"timestamp":" 947589313307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589313702","data":{"timestamp":" 947589313702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589316419","data":{"timestamp":" 947589316418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589318142","data":{"timestamp":" 947589318141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589318932","data":{"timestamp":" 947589318932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589319821","data":{"timestamp":" 947589319820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589320972","data":{"timestamp":" 947589320972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589323388","data":{"timestamp":" 947589323388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589325074","data":{"timestamp":" 947589325074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589325610","data":{"timestamp":" 947589325609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589326257","data":{"timestamp":" 947589326257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589327367","data":{"timestamp":" 947589327366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589328770","data":{"timestamp":" 947589328769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589329673","data":{"timestamp":" 947589329672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589330171","data":{"timestamp":" 947589330170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589330802","data":{"timestamp":" 947589330801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589331261","data":{"timestamp":" 947589331260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589332106","data":{"timestamp":" 947589332106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo ndoto ilivyokuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589334491","data":{"timestamp":" 947589334491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589336297","data":{"timestamp":" 947589336297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589339217","data":{"timestamp":" 947589339216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYEFANANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589340399","data":{"timestamp":" 947589340399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589342377","data":{"timestamp":" 947589342376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589343542","data":{"timestamp":" 947589343541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589344471","data":{"timestamp":" 947589344471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589345886","data":{"timestamp":" 947589345885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589347559","data":{"timestamp":" 947589347559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589349229","data":{"timestamp":" 947589349228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589352303","data":{"timestamp":" 947589352303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589355230","data":{"timestamp":" 947589355229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNGA"," userResponse":" START_AKIMCHUNGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589360587","data":{"timestamp":" 947589360587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589362663","data":{"timestamp":" 947589362662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589364113","data":{"timestamp":" 947589364112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFANANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFANANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589364319","data":{"timestamp":" 947589364319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589365520","data":{"timestamp":" 947589365519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589366492","data":{"timestamp":" 947589366492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589367723","data":{"timestamp":" 947589367722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliyefanana na nyanyake alikuwa akimchunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNGA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589370128","data":{"timestamp":" 947589370128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589371451","data":{"timestamp":" 947589371451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589371961","data":{"timestamp":" 947589371961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589377933","data":{"timestamp":" 947589377932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_ALITABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589379441","data":{"timestamp":" 947589379441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_ALITABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589381493","data":{"timestamp":" 947589381492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589382570","data":{"timestamp":" 947589382570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589384237","data":{"timestamp":" 947589384237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589386175","data":{"timestamp":" 947589386175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589387063","data":{"timestamp":" 947589387063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589388637","data":{"timestamp":" 947589388637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589389191","data":{"timestamp":" 947589389191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589390152","data":{"timestamp":" 947589390152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589391101","data":{"timestamp":" 947589391101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589391551","data":{"timestamp":" 947589391550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589392918","data":{"timestamp":" 947589392918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589395132","data":{"timestamp":" 947589395132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589396940","data":{"timestamp":" 947589396940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589399035","data":{"timestamp":" 947589399034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589399709","data":{"timestamp":" 947589399708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589401400","data":{"timestamp":" 947589401399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ALITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589402022","data":{"timestamp":" 947589402021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589402638","data":{"timestamp":" 947589402637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589403359","data":{"timestamp":" 947589403358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589404412","data":{"timestamp":" 947589404411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589404682","data":{"timestamp":" 947589404681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589405384","data":{"timestamp":" 947589405383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589405583","data":{"timestamp":" 947589405583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589406296","data":{"timestamp":" 947589406296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyo alitabasamu na kumpa kikombe kikubwa cha maziwa ya ngamia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589409774","data":{"timestamp":" 947589409774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589414273","data":{"timestamp":" 947589414273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589414339","data":{"timestamp":" 947589414339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589417788","data":{"timestamp":" 947589417787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFANANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589419876","data":{"timestamp":" 947589419875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589420048","data":{"timestamp":" 947589420048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589421209","data":{"timestamp":" 947589421208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589422978","data":{"timestamp":" 947589422978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589425405","data":{"timestamp":" 947589425405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" KUCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589427197","data":{"timestamp":" 947589427197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589428901","data":{"timestamp":" 947589428901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589429678","data":{"timestamp":" 947589429678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589432951","data":{"timestamp":" 947589432951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589434809","data":{"timestamp":" 947589434808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589436459","data":{"timestamp":" 947589436458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," userResponse":" ALIPOUNYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589437193","data":{"timestamp":" 947589437192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589437586","data":{"timestamp":" 947589437586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589438442","data":{"timestamp":" 947589438442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" KUCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589439224","data":{"timestamp":" 947589439223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589439908","data":{"timestamp":" 947589439907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589441278","data":{"timestamp":" 947589441278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipounyoosha mkono wake kuchukuwa maziwa hivi aliamka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589444983","data":{"timestamp":" 947589444982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589446424","data":{"timestamp":" 947589446424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589449666","data":{"timestamp":" 947589449666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589451775","data":{"timestamp":" 947589451774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589454161","data":{"timestamp":" 947589454160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589454251","data":{"timestamp":" 947589454251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589455714","data":{"timestamp":" 947589455714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589460267","data":{"timestamp":" 947589460266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589462477","data":{"timestamp":" 947589462477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589464264","data":{"timestamp":" 947589464263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589465653","data":{"timestamp":" 947589465652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIYAFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589466178","data":{"timestamp":" 947589466177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589466726","data":{"timestamp":" 947589466725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589467336","data":{"timestamp":" 947589467335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589468544","data":{"timestamp":" 947589468543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliyafungua macho yake pole pole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589472124","data":{"timestamp":" 947589472124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOANGALIA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589473076","data":{"timestamp":" 947589473075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOANGALIA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589475102","data":{"timestamp":" 947589475102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOANGALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589476173","data":{"timestamp":" 947589476172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589476895","data":{"timestamp":" 947589476895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMWONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589478187","data":{"timestamp":" 947589478187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589479100","data":{"timestamp":" 947589479100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589480008","data":{"timestamp":" 947589480008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589482394","data":{"timestamp":" 947589482394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589483517","data":{"timestamp":" 947589483517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589484012","data":{"timestamp":" 947589484012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589484023","data":{"timestamp":" 947589484023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589485794","data":{"timestamp":" 947589485794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589486683","data":{"timestamp":" 947589486683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589488400","data":{"timestamp":" 947589488399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589491292","data":{"timestamp":" 947589491291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMETULIA"," userResponse":" START_AMETULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589492761","data":{"timestamp":" 947589492761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMETULIA"," userResponse":" START_AMETULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589494615","data":{"timestamp":" 947589494614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMETULIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589496015","data":{"timestamp":" 947589496014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" START_AMETULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589497185","data":{"timestamp":" 947589497184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589499271","data":{"timestamp":" 947589499271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589501938","data":{"timestamp":" 947589501938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589502557","data":{"timestamp":" 947589502556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589504036","data":{"timestamp":" 947589504035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589504513","data":{"timestamp":" 947589504512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589505025","data":{"timestamp":" 947589505024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589505438","data":{"timestamp":" 947589505438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589506032","data":{"timestamp":" 947589506032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589506121","data":{"timestamp":" 947589506121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589506670","data":{"timestamp":" 947589506669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589508135","data":{"timestamp":" 947589508135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589509107","data":{"timestamp":" 947589509106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMETULIA"," userResponse":" AMETULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589509577","data":{"timestamp":" 947589509576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589510200","data":{"timestamp":" 947589510199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoangalia juu alimwona ndege mdogo wa rangi ya bluu akiwa ametulia kwenye tawi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589513629","data":{"timestamp":" 947589513629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589515453","data":{"timestamp":" 947589515452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589516957","data":{"timestamp":" 947589516956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589517513","data":{"timestamp":" 947589517513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589522243","data":{"timestamp":" 947589522242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589526776","data":{"timestamp":" 947589526775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589529945","data":{"timestamp":" 947589529945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589531271","data":{"timestamp":" 947589531271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589533039","data":{"timestamp":" 947589533039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPAPATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589534998","data":{"timestamp":" 947589534997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589535158","data":{"timestamp":" 947589535157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589537045","data":{"timestamp":" 947589537045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589537739","data":{"timestamp":" 947589537739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589541081","data":{"timestamp":" 947589541081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589542931","data":{"timestamp":" 947589542931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589543659","data":{"timestamp":" 947589543659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589547205","data":{"timestamp":" 947589547205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," userResponse":" START_AKAMWONGOZEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589549244","data":{"timestamp":" 947589549243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589549917","data":{"timestamp":" 947589549917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589551749","data":{"timestamp":" 947589551748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPAPATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589552718","data":{"timestamp":" 947589552718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589554494","data":{"timestamp":" 947589554493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589556075","data":{"timestamp":" 947589556074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589556962","data":{"timestamp":" 947589556961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589557527","data":{"timestamp":" 947589557527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589558915","data":{"timestamp":" 947589558914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589559535","data":{"timestamp":" 947589559534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589560124","data":{"timestamp":" 947589560123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589561036","data":{"timestamp":" 947589561035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589562188","data":{"timestamp":" 947589562188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," userResponse":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589562999","data":{"timestamp":" 947589562998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589563629","data":{"timestamp":" 947589563628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai aliposimama yule ndege alipapatika mbawa zake kisha akamwongozea Akai njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589565242","data":{"timestamp":" 947589565242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589566934","data":{"timestamp":" 947589566934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" AKAMWONGOZEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589569266","data":{"timestamp":" 947589569265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589571291","data":{"timestamp":" 947589571290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589572443","data":{"timestamp":" 947589572443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOSIMAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589573086","data":{"timestamp":" 947589573085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589574209","data":{"timestamp":" 947589574208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589628812","data":{"timestamp":" 947589628811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589628907","data":{"timestamp":" 947589628907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 741b5f99-ca31-4c54-93ae-743dc3defedc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alimfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589655961","data":{"timestamp":" 947589655961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ake"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589669954","data":{"timestamp":" 947589669954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589679565","data":{"timestamp":" 947589679564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589689708","data":{"timestamp":" 947589689708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589698501","data":{"timestamp":" 947589698500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_ku"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589706806","data":{"timestamp":" 947589706806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t_pe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589716955","data":{"timestamp":" 947589716955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589726275","data":{"timestamp":" 947589726275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589735307","data":{"timestamp":" 947589735307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589744205","data":{"timestamp":" 947589744205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m_ji"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589757908","data":{"timestamp":" 947589757906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 9c680faa-940e-491e-b689-a953d7d3dff2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_m_ji"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589785229","data":{"timestamp":" 947589785229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__lila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589793877","data":{"timestamp":" 947589793876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589806099","data":{"timestamp":" 947589806099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589813029","data":{"timestamp":" 947589813029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589820909","data":{"timestamp":" 947589820909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__enge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589829723","data":{"timestamp":" 947589829723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__mri"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589838859","data":{"timestamp":" 947589838859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__buzi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589848320","data":{"timestamp":" 947589848320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eno"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589859046","data":{"timestamp":" 947589859045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__eusi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589883288","data":{"timestamp":" 947589883287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__ebu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589893727","data":{"timestamp":" 947589893727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__keno"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589902915","data":{"timestamp":" 947589902915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write__huru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.4.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589916620","data":{"timestamp":" 947589916618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 04049aae-e341-434d-a4a1-7dee5e202891"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.4.init.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write__huru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589930563","data":{"timestamp":" 947589930562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589931159","data":{"timestamp":" 947589931158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589931405","data":{"timestamp":" 947589931404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589932055","data":{"timestamp":" 947589932054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589933378","data":{"timestamp":" 947589933376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589933864","data":{"timestamp":" 947589933863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589934051","data":{"timestamp":" 947589934050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589934608","data":{"timestamp":" 947589934608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589937156","data":{"timestamp":" 947589937155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589938092","data":{"timestamp":" 947589938091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589939063","data":{"timestamp":" 947589939062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589940070","data":{"timestamp":" 947589940070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589940678","data":{"timestamp":" 947589940677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589941877","data":{"timestamp":" 947589941877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589942895","data":{"timestamp":" 947589942895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589945061","data":{"timestamp":" 947589945060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589946509","data":{"timestamp":" 947589946509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589949946","data":{"timestamp":" 947589949946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589951592","data":{"timestamp":" 947589951592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589952988","data":{"timestamp":" 947589952988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589956517","data":{"timestamp":" 947589956516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589957727","data":{"timestamp":" 947589957726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" LIKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589958689","data":{"timestamp":" 947589958688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDOKANDO"," userResponse":" KANDOKANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589958944","data":{"timestamp":" 947589958943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589959497","data":{"timestamp":" 947589959496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589960899","data":{"timestamp":" 947589960898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" LILIWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589961743","data":{"timestamp":" 947589961743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589962497","data":{"timestamp":" 947589962497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589964817","data":{"timestamp":" 947589964817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589966322","data":{"timestamp":" 947589966322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589968208","data":{"timestamp":" 947589968208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589969660","data":{"timestamp":" 947589969659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" LIKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589970615","data":{"timestamp":" 947589970615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KANDOKANDO"," userResponse":" START_KANDOKANDO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589971956","data":{"timestamp":" 947589971955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDOKANDO"," userResponse":" KANDOKANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589971959","data":{"timestamp":" 947589971959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589973166","data":{"timestamp":" 947589973166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589975853","data":{"timestamp":" 947589975852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589979540","data":{"timestamp":" 947589979539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589981409","data":{"timestamp":" 947589981408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIWAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589984863","data":{"timestamp":" 947589984863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589986510","data":{"timestamp":" 947589986510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilipokuwa likitembea kandokando mwa ziwa liliwaona wasichana watatu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589989066","data":{"timestamp":" 947589989065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" LIKAWAULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589989736","data":{"timestamp":" 947589989735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589990272","data":{"timestamp":" 947589990272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589990827","data":{"timestamp":" 947589990826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589991312","data":{"timestamp":" 947589991312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589992373","data":{"timestamp":" 947589992372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589992602","data":{"timestamp":" 947589992601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589993247","data":{"timestamp":" 947589993247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589993756","data":{"timestamp":" 947589993755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589994738","data":{"timestamp":" 947589994738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589997098","data":{"timestamp":" 947589997098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" START_LIKAWAULIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589997824","data":{"timestamp":" 947589997824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947589999668","data":{"timestamp":" 947589999667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAWAULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590001714","data":{"timestamp":" 947590001714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590003149","data":{"timestamp":" 947590003149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590004535","data":{"timestamp":" 947590004534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590006333","data":{"timestamp":" 947590006333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590007406","data":{"timestamp":" 947590007406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590007409","data":{"timestamp":" 947590007409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590008245","data":{"timestamp":" 947590008245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" START_ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590009302","data":{"timestamp":" 947590009301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590011444","data":{"timestamp":" 947590011444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590012215","data":{"timestamp":" 947590012215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590013568","data":{"timestamp":" 947590013568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590014454","data":{"timestamp":" 947590014453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590015743","data":{"timestamp":" 947590015743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590015871","data":{"timestamp":" 947590015871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Likawauliza Ni nani kati yenu anayependwa na wazazi wote wawili?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590018366","data":{"timestamp":" 947590018365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590018552","data":{"timestamp":" 947590018551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590019091","data":{"timestamp":" 947590019091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590019981","data":{"timestamp":" 947590019981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590021112","data":{"timestamp":" 947590021111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590021974","data":{"timestamp":" 947590021973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590022724","data":{"timestamp":" 947590022723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590024718","data":{"timestamp":" 947590024718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590025417","data":{"timestamp":" 947590025417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590025614","data":{"timestamp":" 947590025614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590026314","data":{"timestamp":" 947590026313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590027616","data":{"timestamp":" 947590027615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590028535","data":{"timestamp":" 947590028535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590029013","data":{"timestamp":" 947590029013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msichana wa kwanza akasema Mamangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590031044","data":{"timestamp":" 947590031043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590031905","data":{"timestamp":" 947590031904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590033037","data":{"timestamp":" 947590033037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590033769","data":{"timestamp":" 947590033767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590034519","data":{"timestamp":" 947590034518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590036851","data":{"timestamp":" 947590036851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590037756","data":{"timestamp":" 947590037755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590038554","data":{"timestamp":" 947590038554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" START_BABANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590039986","data":{"timestamp":" 947590039986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590041527","data":{"timestamp":" 947590041526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590042498","data":{"timestamp":" 947590042498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590044514","data":{"timestamp":" 947590044514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNIPENDA"," userResponse":" HUNIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590045902","data":{"timestamp":" 947590045901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwingine akasema Babangu hunipenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590047821","data":{"timestamp":" 947590047820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590047995","data":{"timestamp":" 947590047994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590048625","data":{"timestamp":" 947590048624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590049486","data":{"timestamp":" 947590049485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590051268","data":{"timestamp":" 947590051267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDWA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590051526","data":{"timestamp":" 947590051526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590052231","data":{"timestamp":" 947590052230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590052799","data":{"timestamp":" 947590052799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590053427","data":{"timestamp":" 947590053426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590056858","data":{"timestamp":" 947590056858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590057846","data":{"timestamp":" 947590057845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590058214","data":{"timestamp":" 947590058214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590060440","data":{"timestamp":" 947590060440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" START_AKASEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590062184","data":{"timestamp":" 947590062184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590064513","data":{"timestamp":" 947590064512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDWA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590066174","data":{"timestamp":" 947590066174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDWA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590067071","data":{"timestamp":" 947590067071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590067683","data":{"timestamp":" 947590067682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590068756","data":{"timestamp":" 947590068756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590069484","data":{"timestamp":" 947590069484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wa tatu akasema Ninapendwa na wazazi wote sawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590071742","data":{"timestamp":" 947590071742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590072260","data":{"timestamp":" 947590072259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590073471","data":{"timestamp":" 947590073470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590074490","data":{"timestamp":" 947590074490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590075454","data":{"timestamp":" 947590075454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590075700","data":{"timestamp":" 947590075699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590076258","data":{"timestamp":" 947590076257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590077031","data":{"timestamp":" 947590077031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590079043","data":{"timestamp":" 947590079043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" ALIFUATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590081165","data":{"timestamp":" 947590081165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALISAIDIE"," userResponse":" AKALISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590082118","data":{"timestamp":" 947590082118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINUA"," userResponse":" KUINUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590082727","data":{"timestamp":" 947590082726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TITA"," userResponse":" TITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590082956","data":{"timestamp":" 947590082956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590083518","data":{"timestamp":" 947590083518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590084493","data":{"timestamp":" 947590084492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590088023","data":{"timestamp":" 947590088023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590089328","data":{"timestamp":" 947590089328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590089933","data":{"timestamp":" 947590089933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_LIKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590090757","data":{"timestamp":" 947590090757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" START_LIKAMWAMBIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590093163","data":{"timestamp":" 947590093162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590094611","data":{"timestamp":" 947590094610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590096433","data":{"timestamp":" 947590096433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAYEPENDWA"," userResponse":" ANAYEPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590096833","data":{"timestamp":" 947590096832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590097549","data":{"timestamp":" 947590097548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590098829","data":{"timestamp":" 947590098829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590100264","data":{"timestamp":" 947590100263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" START_ALIFUATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590101088","data":{"timestamp":" 947590101088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590102977","data":{"timestamp":" 947590102976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590104949","data":{"timestamp":" 947590104949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALISAIDIE"," userResponse":" AKALISAIDIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590107015","data":{"timestamp":" 947590107015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINUA"," userResponse":" KUINUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590108254","data":{"timestamp":" 947590108254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TITA"," userResponse":" TITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590111244","data":{"timestamp":" 947590111244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590112507","data":{"timestamp":" 947590112507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590113816","data":{"timestamp":" 947590113816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590114978","data":{"timestamp":" 947590114977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590116300","data":{"timestamp":" 947590116300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590118018","data":{"timestamp":" 947590118018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha jitu likamwambia msichana anayependwa na wazazi wote alifuate akalisaidie kuinua tita la kuni mgongoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590119460","data":{"timestamp":" 947590119459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590120289","data":{"timestamp":" 947590120289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590121267","data":{"timestamp":" 947590121266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590121885","data":{"timestamp":" 947590121884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590123193","data":{"timestamp":" 947590123192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALILIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590123821","data":{"timestamp":" 947590123820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590125725","data":{"timestamp":" 947590125725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590126106","data":{"timestamp":" 947590126105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590127025","data":{"timestamp":" 947590127025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590127722","data":{"timestamp":" 947590127722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590128897","data":{"timestamp":" 947590128897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590130335","data":{"timestamp":" 947590130335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590132230","data":{"timestamp":" 947590132229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590133600","data":{"timestamp":" 947590133600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo msichana huyo alilifuata jitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590135844","data":{"timestamp":" 947590135844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590136048","data":{"timestamp":" 947590136047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590136877","data":{"timestamp":" 947590136877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590137684","data":{"timestamp":" 947590137683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590138674","data":{"timestamp":" 947590138673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590139894","data":{"timestamp":" 947590139894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AKALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590140474","data":{"timestamp":" 947590140474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590141515","data":{"timestamp":" 947590141514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590141961","data":{"timestamp":" 947590141961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590142760","data":{"timestamp":" 947590142760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590145220","data":{"timestamp":" 947590145220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590146136","data":{"timestamp":" 947590146136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590148122","data":{"timestamp":" 947590148122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590148917","data":{"timestamp":" 947590148917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" START_KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590150132","data":{"timestamp":" 947590150131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590151782","data":{"timestamp":" 947590151781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590153238","data":{"timestamp":" 947590153237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590156975","data":{"timestamp":" 947590156974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590158029","data":{"timestamp":" 947590158028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590160162","data":{"timestamp":" 947590160162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590161527","data":{"timestamp":" 947590161527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590162454","data":{"timestamp":" 947590162453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590164103","data":{"timestamp":" 947590164102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590164665","data":{"timestamp":" 947590164665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590164785","data":{"timestamp":" 947590164785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutembea kidogo msichana akaliuliza jitu Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590166558","data":{"timestamp":" 947590166557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590167507","data":{"timestamp":" 947590167506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590168278","data":{"timestamp":" 947590168277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" ZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590168904","data":{"timestamp":" 947590168903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590169112","data":{"timestamp":" 947590169111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590169640","data":{"timestamp":" 947590169639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590170249","data":{"timestamp":" 947590170248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590171200","data":{"timestamp":" 947590171200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590176256","data":{"timestamp":" 947590176256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590177399","data":{"timestamp":" 947590177399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590178841","data":{"timestamp":" 947590178841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590180615","data":{"timestamp":" 947590180615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590182459","data":{"timestamp":" 947590182458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590183364","data":{"timestamp":" 947590183364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590184289","data":{"timestamp":" 947590184289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" ZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590186783","data":{"timestamp":" 947590186783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590188482","data":{"timestamp":" 947590188482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590189738","data":{"timestamp":" 947590189738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590190871","data":{"timestamp":" 947590190870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590191814","data":{"timestamp":" 947590191813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590195567","data":{"timestamp":" 947590195567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Ziko karibu na ile miti pale!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590198464","data":{"timestamp":" 947590198463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590198959","data":{"timestamp":" 947590198958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590199423","data":{"timestamp":" 947590199422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590200062","data":{"timestamp":" 947590200062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590200833","data":{"timestamp":" 947590200832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590201754","data":{"timestamp":" 947590201753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAULIZA"," userResponse":" AKAULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590202218","data":{"timestamp":" 947590202218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590202748","data":{"timestamp":" 947590202747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590203689","data":{"timestamp":" 947590203688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590204118","data":{"timestamp":" 947590204118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590204951","data":{"timestamp":" 947590204950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590208845","data":{"timestamp":" 947590208845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590210344","data":{"timestamp":" 947590210343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590212421","data":{"timestamp":" 947590212421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590213366","data":{"timestamp":" 947590213365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590214266","data":{"timestamp":" 947590214265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590217039","data":{"timestamp":" 947590217039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590219145","data":{"timestamp":" 947590219144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAULIZA"," userResponse":" START_AKAULIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590220111","data":{"timestamp":" 947590220111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKAULIZA"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590221902","data":{"timestamp":" 947590221901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590223696","data":{"timestamp":" 947590223696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590224071","data":{"timestamp":" 947590224070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590226084","data":{"timestamp":" 947590226083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590227009","data":{"timestamp":" 947590227008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590227982","data":{"timestamp":" 947590227981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kwenye miti hiyo msichana akauliza jitu tena Wapi kuni zako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKO"," userResponse":" ZAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590229680","data":{"timestamp":" 947590229679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590230678","data":{"timestamp":" 947590230677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590231706","data":{"timestamp":" 947590231706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIKO"," userResponse":" HAZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590232084","data":{"timestamp":" 947590232083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590232758","data":{"timestamp":" 947590232757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590234917","data":{"timestamp":" 947590234916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590235506","data":{"timestamp":" 947590235505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" START_LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590237925","data":{"timestamp":" 947590237925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590239333","data":{"timestamp":" 947590239333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIKO"," userResponse":" HAZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590239930","data":{"timestamp":" 947590239930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590240461","data":{"timestamp":" 947590240461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Haziko mbali sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590243468","data":{"timestamp":" 947590243467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590244368","data":{"timestamp":" 947590244367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590246199","data":{"timestamp":" 947590246198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590247376","data":{"timestamp":" 947590247375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590249189","data":{"timestamp":" 947590249189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590252555","data":{"timestamp":" 947590252555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590254860","data":{"timestamp":" 947590254859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKUTANA"," userResponse":" WAKAKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590255066","data":{"timestamp":" 947590255065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590256003","data":{"timestamp":" 947590256003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590257557","data":{"timestamp":" 947590257557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKUTANA"," userResponse":" START_WAKAKUTANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590258977","data":{"timestamp":" 947590258977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKUTANA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590260676","data":{"timestamp":" 947590260675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKUTANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590261949","data":{"timestamp":" 947590261948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590262056","data":{"timestamp":" 947590262056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakakutana na mwanamume."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590264091","data":{"timestamp":" 947590264090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590265361","data":{"timestamp":" 947590265360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AKALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590265909","data":{"timestamp":" 947590265909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590267071","data":{"timestamp":" 947590267070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590267639","data":{"timestamp":" 947590267639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590268130","data":{"timestamp":" 947590268129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590269191","data":{"timestamp":" 947590269190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWAJE"," userResponse":" ANAITWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590271280","data":{"timestamp":" 947590271279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590272860","data":{"timestamp":" 947590272860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALIULIZA"," userResponse":" AKALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590272863","data":{"timestamp":" 947590272863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590274935","data":{"timestamp":" 947590274934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590275340","data":{"timestamp":" 947590275340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590275877","data":{"timestamp":" 947590275877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590276416","data":{"timestamp":" 947590276416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWAJE"," userResponse":" START_ANAITWAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590277255","data":{"timestamp":" 947590277254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWAJE"," userResponse":" START_ANAITWAJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590279122","data":{"timestamp":" 947590279121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWAJE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590280809","data":{"timestamp":" 947590280808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590281709","data":{"timestamp":" 947590281707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590283128","data":{"timestamp":" 947590283128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590283776","data":{"timestamp":" 947590283776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590284967","data":{"timestamp":" 947590284966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZUNGUZAO"," userResponse":" UZUNGUZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590287163","data":{"timestamp":" 947590287163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590287585","data":{"timestamp":" 947590287584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" START_LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590289229","data":{"timestamp":" 947590289229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAJIBU"," userResponse":" LIKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590290131","data":{"timestamp":" 947590290131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" START_ANAITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590291250","data":{"timestamp":" 947590291250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590292374","data":{"timestamp":" 947590292374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590295335","data":{"timestamp":" 947590295335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590296717","data":{"timestamp":" 947590296717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jitu likajibu Anaitwa Mfuko Uzunguzao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZUNGUZAO"," userResponse":" UZUNGUZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590299185","data":{"timestamp":" 947590299184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590300044","data":{"timestamp":" 947590300044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590300660","data":{"timestamp":" 947590300659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590300936","data":{"timestamp":" 947590300935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590301684","data":{"timestamp":" 947590301684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590303048","data":{"timestamp":" 947590303047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590303548","data":{"timestamp":" 947590303547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590303926","data":{"timestamp":" 947590303926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590304939","data":{"timestamp":" 947590304939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590306072","data":{"timestamp":" 947590306071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUKO"," userResponse":" MIFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590307545","data":{"timestamp":" 947590307545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONGEI"," userResponse":" HAIONGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590308590","data":{"timestamp":" 947590308589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAITWA"," userResponse":" NAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590309314","data":{"timestamp":" 947590309314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAAMUNGEI"," userResponse":" KAAMUNGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590309959","data":{"timestamp":" 947590309958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590312219","data":{"timestamp":" 947590312219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590313737","data":{"timestamp":" 947590313737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590315616","data":{"timestamp":" 947590315616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590316267","data":{"timestamp":" 947590316266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590318087","data":{"timestamp":" 947590318087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590319405","data":{"timestamp":" 947590319404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590319918","data":{"timestamp":" 947590319917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590321464","data":{"timestamp":" 947590321464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590322188","data":{"timestamp":" 947590322188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590322507","data":{"timestamp":" 947590322507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590323523","data":{"timestamp":" 947590323523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" KAMWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590325190","data":{"timestamp":" 947590325190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590327678","data":{"timestamp":" 947590327678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUKO"," userResponse":" MIFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590328200","data":{"timestamp":" 947590328200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONGEI"," userResponse":" START_HAIONGEI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590330928","data":{"timestamp":" 947590330928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONGEI"," userResponse":" HAIONGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590331504","data":{"timestamp":" 947590331504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAITWA"," userResponse":" NAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590333909","data":{"timestamp":" 947590333909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAAMUNGEI"," userResponse":" KAAMUNGEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590334311","data":{"timestamp":" 947590334310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590335985","data":{"timestamp":" 947590335984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590337234","data":{"timestamp":" 947590337232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590337618","data":{"timestamp":" 947590337618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590339964","data":{"timestamp":" 947590339964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590340697","data":{"timestamp":" 947590340697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590341538","data":{"timestamp":" 947590341538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590343209","data":{"timestamp":" 947590343208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590344451","data":{"timestamp":" 947590344450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590345191","data":{"timestamp":" 947590345191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590346002","data":{"timestamp":" 947590346001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANYWEA"," userResponse":" NANYWEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590347031","data":{"timestamp":" 947590347030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590348986","data":{"timestamp":" 947590348986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590350086","data":{"timestamp":" 947590350086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" NIMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590350881","data":{"timestamp":" 947590350881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590351708","data":{"timestamp":" 947590351708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANYWEA"," userResponse":" NANYWEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590351892","data":{"timestamp":" 947590351892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590352757","data":{"timestamp":" 947590352756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590354465","data":{"timestamp":" 947590354464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba nimpendaye Kata nanywea maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590357025","data":{"timestamp":" 947590357025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590357572","data":{"timestamp":" 947590357571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590358667","data":{"timestamp":" 947590358666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590359165","data":{"timestamp":" 947590359164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590359381","data":{"timestamp":" 947590359380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590360274","data":{"timestamp":" 947590360273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590362409","data":{"timestamp":" 947590362409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUSURU"," userResponse":" ALIMNUSURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590363081","data":{"timestamp":" 947590363081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590363341","data":{"timestamp":" 947590363341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590364004","data":{"timestamp":" 947590364003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590364619","data":{"timestamp":" 947590364618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590365664","data":{"timestamp":" 947590365663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" KUMRUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590365966","data":{"timestamp":" 947590365966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590366640","data":{"timestamp":" 947590366640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590367203","data":{"timestamp":" 947590367202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590370298","data":{"timestamp":" 947590370298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590370384","data":{"timestamp":" 947590370384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590371772","data":{"timestamp":" 947590371772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590373307","data":{"timestamp":" 947590373305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590377207","data":{"timestamp":" 947590377207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590378583","data":{"timestamp":" 947590378582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590382370","data":{"timestamp":" 947590382369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590383882","data":{"timestamp":" 947590383882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590385374","data":{"timestamp":" 947590385374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590386431","data":{"timestamp":" 947590386430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" START_MSICHANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590388268","data":{"timestamp":" 947590388268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590390195","data":{"timestamp":" 947590390195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUSURU"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590391385","data":{"timestamp":" 947590391384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUSURU"," userResponse":" START_ALIMNUSURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590393302","data":{"timestamp":" 947590393301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUSURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590394990","data":{"timestamp":" 947590394990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590395929","data":{"timestamp":" 947590395929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590396627","data":{"timestamp":" 947590396627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590396631","data":{"timestamp":" 947590396631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JITU"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590398710","data":{"timestamp":" 947590398710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590400843","data":{"timestamp":" 947590400843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590402045","data":{"timestamp":" 947590402045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" JITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590403952","data":{"timestamp":" 947590403951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMRUDISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590407433","data":{"timestamp":" 947590407433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590408925","data":{"timestamp":" 947590408925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590410386","data":{"timestamp":" 947590410385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590411084","data":{"timestamp":" 947590411084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590412284","data":{"timestamp":" 947590412284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume huyo aliposikia wimbo wa msichana alimnusuru kutoka kwa jitu na kumrudisha kwa wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590414332","data":{"timestamp":" 947590414332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590415317","data":{"timestamp":" 947590415316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAISHIA"," userResponse":" INAISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590415830","data":{"timestamp":" 947590415829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590417749","data":{"timestamp":" 947590417748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590418526","data":{"timestamp":" 947590418525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAISHIA"," userResponse":" INAISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590419160","data":{"timestamp":" 947590419160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590421178","data":{"timestamp":" 947590421176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590421277","data":{"timestamp":" 947590421277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590432039","data":{"timestamp":" 947590432039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 0f149345-1a70-4897-8230-bcdec03ddd80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadithi inaishia hapo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590446393","data":{"timestamp":" 947590446392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" KUSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590458093","data":{"timestamp":" 947590458092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590459696","data":{"timestamp":" 947590459695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwengine"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590463934","data":{"timestamp":" 947590463934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwengine"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590465548","data":{"timestamp":" 947590465548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590469013","data":{"timestamp":" 947590469013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590470632","data":{"timestamp":" 947590470631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alifuata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590473728","data":{"timestamp":" 947590473727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alifuata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590475340","data":{"timestamp":" 947590475340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alitumia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" ALITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590478480","data":{"timestamp":" 947590478480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alitumia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" ALITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590480105","data":{"timestamp":" 947590480103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590483363","data":{"timestamp":" 947590483363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590484981","data":{"timestamp":" 947590484980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karatasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590488408","data":{"timestamp":" 947590488407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karatasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590490011","data":{"timestamp":" 947590490011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakaishi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAISHI"," userResponse":" WAKAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590493052","data":{"timestamp":" 947590493051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakaishi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAISHI"," userResponse":" WAKAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590494686","data":{"timestamp":" 947590494686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" ALIMPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590497310","data":{"timestamp":" 947590497309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMPIGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590499613","data":{"timestamp":" 947590499613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMPIGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590501429","data":{"timestamp":" 947590501429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alimpiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590503043","data":{"timestamp":" 947590503042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590508781","data":{"timestamp":" 947590508781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590510794","data":{"timestamp":" 947590510792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590510908","data":{"timestamp":" 947590510908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 65a85fb9-4abb-44d7-8498-67d5cfa20cb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikitokea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590532540","data":{"timestamp":" 947590532540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590533192","data":{"timestamp":" 947590533189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590533418","data":{"timestamp":" 947590533417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590534177","data":{"timestamp":" 947590534176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590535527","data":{"timestamp":" 947590535526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590535917","data":{"timestamp":" 947590535916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590536718","data":{"timestamp":" 947590536718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590537707","data":{"timestamp":" 947590537701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590537939","data":{"timestamp":" 947590537938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590538552","data":{"timestamp":" 947590538551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590542167","data":{"timestamp":" 947590542166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590544834","data":{"timestamp":" 947590544834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590546333","data":{"timestamp":" 947590546332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590549913","data":{"timestamp":" 947590549913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590552724","data":{"timestamp":" 947590552724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590553841","data":{"timestamp":" 947590553841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590554124","data":{"timestamp":" 947590554124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590555274","data":{"timestamp":" 947590555274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590557284","data":{"timestamp":" 947590557284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590558655","data":{"timestamp":" 947590558655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590559506","data":{"timestamp":" 947590559506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590560605","data":{"timestamp":" 947590560605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590561593","data":{"timestamp":" 947590561592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590562337","data":{"timestamp":" 947590562337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590562834","data":{"timestamp":" 947590562834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590564498","data":{"timestamp":" 947590564497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" START_NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590566084","data":{"timestamp":" 947590566083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale waliishi dada wawili Nelima na Nambuya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590566636","data":{"timestamp":" 947590566636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590567994","data":{"timestamp":" 947590567994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590568517","data":{"timestamp":" 947590568517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590568592","data":{"timestamp":" 947590568592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590569297","data":{"timestamp":" 947590569297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKUFA"," userResponse":" WAMEKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590572958","data":{"timestamp":" 947590572958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590573354","data":{"timestamp":" 947590573353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590574571","data":{"timestamp":" 947590574571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590575402","data":{"timestamp":" 947590575402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590577316","data":{"timestamp":" 947590577316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590579007","data":{"timestamp":" 947590579007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKUFA"," userResponse":" WAMEKUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590581176","data":{"timestamp":" 947590581176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590581845","data":{"timestamp":" 947590581844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590582352","data":{"timestamp":" 947590582352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590583391","data":{"timestamp":" 947590583391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590583689","data":{"timestamp":" 947590583688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590584357","data":{"timestamp":" 947590584356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590586486","data":{"timestamp":" 947590586486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590587430","data":{"timestamp":" 947590587430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590589041","data":{"timestamp":" 947590589041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590589986","data":{"timestamp":" 947590589986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590590321","data":{"timestamp":" 947590590321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590590874","data":{"timestamp":" 947590590873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba lisilokuwa na mimea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590593013","data":{"timestamp":" 947590593012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590593292","data":{"timestamp":" 947590593291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590593900","data":{"timestamp":" 947590593899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590594359","data":{"timestamp":" 947590594358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590595157","data":{"timestamp":" 947590595156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590597271","data":{"timestamp":" 947590597270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590597786","data":{"timestamp":" 947590597786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590598159","data":{"timestamp":" 947590598158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590598690","data":{"timestamp":" 947590598690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590599293","data":{"timestamp":" 947590599292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa na mvua wala chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590601576","data":{"timestamp":" 947590601575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYETAKA"," userResponse":" ALIYETAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590602489","data":{"timestamp":" 947590602488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590604159","data":{"timestamp":" 947590604159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" ALILAZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590604712","data":{"timestamp":" 947590604711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590605370","data":{"timestamp":" 947590605369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590606330","data":{"timestamp":" 947590606329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIPATA"," userResponse":" KUKIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590608735","data":{"timestamp":" 947590608735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYETAKA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYETAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590610560","data":{"timestamp":" 947590610560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYETAKA"," userResponse":" ALIYETAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590611367","data":{"timestamp":" 947590611367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" START_CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590612527","data":{"timestamp":" 947590612527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590614209","data":{"timestamp":" 947590614209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590615454","data":{"timestamp":" 947590615454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590617469","data":{"timestamp":" 947590617468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590618335","data":{"timestamp":" 947590618334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590618918","data":{"timestamp":" 947590618918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590619730","data":{"timestamp":" 947590619730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyetaka chakula alilazimika kwenda mbali kukipata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIPATA"," userResponse":" KUKIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590622253","data":{"timestamp":" 947590622253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590623022","data":{"timestamp":" 947590623021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590624313","data":{"timestamp":" 947590624312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYENYEKEVU"," userResponse":" MNYENYEKEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590626315","data":{"timestamp":" 947590626314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMAVU"," userResponse":" MNYAMAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590627805","data":{"timestamp":" 947590627804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIYEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590628764","data":{"timestamp":" 947590628763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590631482","data":{"timestamp":" 947590631481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590634372","data":{"timestamp":" 947590634372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MNYENYEKEVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590635486","data":{"timestamp":" 947590635486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590637100","data":{"timestamp":" 947590637100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYENYEKEVU"," userResponse":" MNYENYEKEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590639010","data":{"timestamp":" 947590639010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMAVU"," userResponse":" START_MNYAMAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590640853","data":{"timestamp":" 947590640853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMAVU"," userResponse":" MNYAMAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590642654","data":{"timestamp":" 947590642654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" START_ALIYEPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590644478","data":{"timestamp":" 947590644477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIYEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590645578","data":{"timestamp":" 947590645578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" START_KUSAIDIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590648012","data":{"timestamp":" 947590648012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikuwa mnyenyekevu mnyamavu aliyependa kusaidia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590649917","data":{"timestamp":" 947590649916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590650836","data":{"timestamp":" 947590650835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590651817","data":{"timestamp":" 947590651816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590652293","data":{"timestamp":" 947590652293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590653463","data":{"timestamp":" 947590653463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" KIBURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590654043","data":{"timestamp":" 947590654042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590655336","data":{"timestamp":" 947590655335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUMSIKIZA"," userResponse":" HAKUMSIKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590656176","data":{"timestamp":" 947590656175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590659077","data":{"timestamp":" 947590659077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590659080","data":{"timestamp":" 947590659080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590660577","data":{"timestamp":" 947590660577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590661474","data":{"timestamp":" 947590661474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590661780","data":{"timestamp":" 947590661780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" KIBURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590662689","data":{"timestamp":" 947590662689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590663684","data":{"timestamp":" 947590663683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUMSIKIZA"," userResponse":" HAKUMSIKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590664400","data":{"timestamp":" 947590664400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake Nambuya alikuwa mwenye kiburi na hakumsikiza yeyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590667005","data":{"timestamp":" 947590667004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590667501","data":{"timestamp":" 947590667500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590668309","data":{"timestamp":" 947590668308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590670125","data":{"timestamp":" 947590670125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAJALI"," userResponse":" START_HAKUWAJALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590671452","data":{"timestamp":" 947590671452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590672254","data":{"timestamp":" 947590672253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590673002","data":{"timestamp":" 947590673002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590675091","data":{"timestamp":" 947590675091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwajali watu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590677510","data":{"timestamp":" 947590677509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590677967","data":{"timestamp":" 947590677967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590678440","data":{"timestamp":" 947590678440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590679017","data":{"timestamp":" 947590679016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590680045","data":{"timestamp":" 947590680044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590680799","data":{"timestamp":" 947590680799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590681691","data":{"timestamp":" 947590681690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUNDUA"," userResponse":" KUGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590682328","data":{"timestamp":" 947590682327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590683559","data":{"timestamp":" 947590683559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590683849","data":{"timestamp":" 947590683848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590684681","data":{"timestamp":" 947590684680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590684959","data":{"timestamp":" 947590684959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590685558","data":{"timestamp":" 947590685558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590687307","data":{"timestamp":" 947590687307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590688001","data":{"timestamp":" 947590688000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590689311","data":{"timestamp":" 947590689310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590690273","data":{"timestamp":" 947590690272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590691919","data":{"timestamp":" 947590691919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590692748","data":{"timestamp":" 947590692747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590694661","data":{"timestamp":" 947590694660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590695542","data":{"timestamp":" 947590695542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590696118","data":{"timestamp":" 947590696118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUNDUA"," userResponse":" KUGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590697222","data":{"timestamp":" 947590697221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590698534","data":{"timestamp":" 947590698534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" START_HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590699610","data":{"timestamp":" 947590699609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590701523","data":{"timestamp":" 947590701523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590702004","data":{"timestamp":" 947590702004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590703099","data":{"timestamp":" 947590703099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590703103","data":{"timestamp":" 947590703103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590703815","data":{"timestamp":" 947590703815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590704409","data":{"timestamp":" 947590704409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590711121","data":{"timestamp":" 947590711120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja dada hao waliamka na kugundua kwamba hawakuwa na chochote cha kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590713871","data":{"timestamp":" 947590713870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" WALILAZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590714852","data":{"timestamp":" 947590714851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590715673","data":{"timestamp":" 947590715672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590717530","data":{"timestamp":" 947590717530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590719183","data":{"timestamp":" 947590719183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590721532","data":{"timestamp":" 947590721531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590723711","data":{"timestamp":" 947590723710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590723793","data":{"timestamp":" 947590723793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilazimika kutafuta chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590725208","data":{"timestamp":" 947590725207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590725734","data":{"timestamp":" 947590725733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590726465","data":{"timestamp":" 947590726463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590726642","data":{"timestamp":" 947590726642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590727558","data":{"timestamp":" 947590727557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590728911","data":{"timestamp":" 947590728911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590729725","data":{"timestamp":" 947590729725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590730445","data":{"timestamp":" 947590730444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590731316","data":{"timestamp":" 947590731315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590732328","data":{"timestamp":" 947590732327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590733973","data":{"timestamp":" 947590733973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590735056","data":{"timestamp":" 947590735056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590735060","data":{"timestamp":" 947590735060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590735065","data":{"timestamp":" 947590735065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590735594","data":{"timestamp":" 947590735594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" START_NAMBUYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590736827","data":{"timestamp":" 947590736826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590738431","data":{"timestamp":" 947590738431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590738605","data":{"timestamp":" 947590738605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590740631","data":{"timestamp":" 947590740631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590742121","data":{"timestamp":" 947590742121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590743216","data":{"timestamp":" 947590743216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590744448","data":{"timestamp":" 947590744448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590745242","data":{"timestamp":" 947590745242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590746400","data":{"timestamp":" 947590746400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590748125","data":{"timestamp":" 947590748125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nelima na Nambuya walikwenda kila mmoja upande tofauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590750644","data":{"timestamp":" 947590750643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590751211","data":{"timestamp":" 947590751210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590752228","data":{"timestamp":" 947590752227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590752937","data":{"timestamp":" 947590752936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590753795","data":{"timestamp":" 947590753795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590754618","data":{"timestamp":" 947590754618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590755260","data":{"timestamp":" 947590755259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590755719","data":{"timestamp":" 947590755717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590756691","data":{"timestamp":" 947590756690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590759439","data":{"timestamp":" 947590759438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590761074","data":{"timestamp":" 947590761074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590762750","data":{"timestamp":" 947590762749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590765536","data":{"timestamp":" 947590765536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590766686","data":{"timestamp":" 947590766685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590768094","data":{"timestamp":" 947590768093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590769037","data":{"timestamp":" 947590769037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590771156","data":{"timestamp":" 947590771156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590772794","data":{"timestamp":" 947590772793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590774972","data":{"timestamp":" 947590774971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590776274","data":{"timestamp":" 947590776274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590776659","data":{"timestamp":" 947590776658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590778671","data":{"timestamp":" 947590778671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590780067","data":{"timestamp":" 947590780067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" START_NETASILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590783956","data":{"timestamp":" 947590783956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo paliishi mwanamke mkongwe kwa jina Netasile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590786531","data":{"timestamp":" 947590786530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMINIWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMINIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590787443","data":{"timestamp":" 947590787442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPEANA"," userResponse":" KUPEANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590788414","data":{"timestamp":" 947590788414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAJIRI"," userResponse":" UTAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590790848","data":{"timestamp":" 947590790847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMINIWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMINIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590791270","data":{"timestamp":" 947590791269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPEANA"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590792778","data":{"timestamp":" 947590792777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPEANA"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590794294","data":{"timestamp":" 947590794294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPEANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590795884","data":{"timestamp":" 947590795883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UTAJIRI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590797890","data":{"timestamp":" 947590797889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliaminiwa kupeana utajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAJIRI"," userResponse":" UTAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590799951","data":{"timestamp":" 947590799950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590800861","data":{"timestamp":" 947590800861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590801122","data":{"timestamp":" 947590801122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590801885","data":{"timestamp":" 947590801885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGONJWA"," userResponse":" UGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590802103","data":{"timestamp":" 947590802103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590802925","data":{"timestamp":" 947590802924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOMA"," userResponse":" UKOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590803497","data":{"timestamp":" 947590803495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590803937","data":{"timestamp":" 947590803936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590804467","data":{"timestamp":" 947590804466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590805601","data":{"timestamp":" 947590805601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJAA"," userResponse":" ULIJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590806521","data":{"timestamp":" 947590806521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" VIDONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590808324","data":{"timestamp":" 947590808324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590809632","data":{"timestamp":" 947590809632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590810337","data":{"timestamp":" 947590810337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590815123","data":{"timestamp":" 947590815123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGONJWA"," userResponse":" UGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590815127","data":{"timestamp":" 947590815127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590815684","data":{"timestamp":" 947590815684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOMA"," userResponse":" UKOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590817689","data":{"timestamp":" 947590817689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590819425","data":{"timestamp":" 947590819423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590821119","data":{"timestamp":" 947590821119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590822441","data":{"timestamp":" 947590822441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJAA"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590823689","data":{"timestamp":" 947590823689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJAA"," userResponse":" VIDONDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590825577","data":{"timestamp":" 947590825576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590826667","data":{"timestamp":" 947590826667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Netasile alikuwa na ugonjwa wa ukoma na mwili wake ulijaa vidonda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" VIDONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590829613","data":{"timestamp":" 947590829612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590830694","data":{"timestamp":" 947590830694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATANA"," userResponse":" ALIPATANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590830894","data":{"timestamp":" 947590830893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590831683","data":{"timestamp":" 947590831683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590832302","data":{"timestamp":" 947590832302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590833392","data":{"timestamp":" 947590833391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590834702","data":{"timestamp":" 947590834701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" MWANANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590835377","data":{"timestamp":" 947590835376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590835927","data":{"timestamp":" 947590835927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590836901","data":{"timestamp":" 947590836899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590839875","data":{"timestamp":" 947590839875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590841785","data":{"timestamp":" 947590841785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" START_NAMBUYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590843395","data":{"timestamp":" 947590843395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590846725","data":{"timestamp":" 947590846725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATANA"," userResponse":" ALIPATANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590847624","data":{"timestamp":" 947590847624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590849874","data":{"timestamp":" 947590849873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" START_MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590851925","data":{"timestamp":" 947590851925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590853296","data":{"timestamp":" 947590853296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590855068","data":{"timestamp":" 947590855068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590858546","data":{"timestamp":" 947590858546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" MWANANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590860233","data":{"timestamp":" 947590860233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590861586","data":{"timestamp":" 947590861585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590861600","data":{"timestamp":" 947590861599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590861696","data":{"timestamp":" 947590861695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alipatana na mwanamke huyo aliyemwita Mwanangu u hali gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590863832","data":{"timestamp":" 947590863831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATOKA"," userResponse":" UNATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590864702","data":{"timestamp":" 947590864702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590866974","data":{"timestamp":" 947590866973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNATOKA"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590867996","data":{"timestamp":" 947590867996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNATOKA"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590869779","data":{"timestamp":" 947590869778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590870744","data":{"timestamp":" 947590870744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590872385","data":{"timestamp":" 947590872385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unatoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590874542","data":{"timestamp":" 947590874542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKWENDA"," userResponse":" UNAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590875431","data":{"timestamp":" 947590875430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590877639","data":{"timestamp":" 947590877637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKWENDA"," userResponse":" UNAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590878230","data":{"timestamp":" 947590878230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unakwenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590880835","data":{"timestamp":" 947590880834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590881702","data":{"timestamp":" 947590881701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590882661","data":{"timestamp":" 947590882660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590883308","data":{"timestamp":" 947590883307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590885666","data":{"timestamp":" 947590885665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590887383","data":{"timestamp":" 947590887382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590888342","data":{"timestamp":" 947590888341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590890474","data":{"timestamp":" 947590890474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590896743","data":{"timestamp":" 947590896743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alijibu maswali yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590898467","data":{"timestamp":" 947590898466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590899326","data":{"timestamp":" 947590899325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590900356","data":{"timestamp":" 947590900356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590901616","data":{"timestamp":" 947590901616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590902315","data":{"timestamp":" 947590902314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIBEBE"," userResponse":" UNIBEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590903828","data":{"timestamp":" 947590903828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIPELEKE"," userResponse":" UNIPELEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590904673","data":{"timestamp":" 947590904671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590905334","data":{"timestamp":" 947590905333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590906287","data":{"timestamp":" 947590906286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590907430","data":{"timestamp":" 947590907430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590907671","data":{"timestamp":" 947590907670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590908503","data":{"timestamp":" 947590908502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590911153","data":{"timestamp":" 947590911152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590914651","data":{"timestamp":" 947590914650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590918950","data":{"timestamp":" 947590918950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590922518","data":{"timestamp":" 947590922517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590924365","data":{"timestamp":" 947590924365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590925332","data":{"timestamp":" 947590925331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590927058","data":{"timestamp":" 947590927057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" START_NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590928367","data":{"timestamp":" 947590928366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590929147","data":{"timestamp":" 947590929146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNIBEBE"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590930585","data":{"timestamp":" 947590930584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNIBEBE"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590932280","data":{"timestamp":" 947590932280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIBEBE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590934564","data":{"timestamp":" 947590934564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNIPELEKE"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590935880","data":{"timestamp":" 947590935879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNIPELEKE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590937893","data":{"timestamp":" 947590937893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNIPELEKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590939685","data":{"timestamp":" 947590939685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590940880","data":{"timestamp":" 947590940879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590942594","data":{"timestamp":" 947590942593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590945561","data":{"timestamp":" 947590945561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590947114","data":{"timestamp":" 947590947113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590948448","data":{"timestamp":" 947590948446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590952841","data":{"timestamp":" 947590952841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" START_NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590955469","data":{"timestamp":" 947590955469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590956963","data":{"timestamp":" 947590956963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590962168","data":{"timestamp":" 947590962168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590963431","data":{"timestamp":" 947590963431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590964927","data":{"timestamp":" 947590964927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mwanamke akasema Njoo unibebe unipeleke nyumbani kwangu nami nitakwambia la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590966970","data":{"timestamp":" 947590966969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590968472","data":{"timestamp":" 947590968471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590969522","data":{"timestamp":" 947590969521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" KIBURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590973177","data":{"timestamp":" 947590973177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590976365","data":{"timestamp":" 947590976365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590977948","data":{"timestamp":" 947590977946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590978268","data":{"timestamp":" 947590978268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590979964","data":{"timestamp":" 947590979963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590981873","data":{"timestamp":" 947590981872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590983345","data":{"timestamp":" 947590983345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590985270","data":{"timestamp":" 947590985270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alimwonyesha kiburi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBURI"," userResponse":" KIBURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590987954","data":{"timestamp":" 947590987954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590989334","data":{"timestamp":" 947590989333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590990035","data":{"timestamp":" 947590990034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFE"," userResponse":" NIFE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590991145","data":{"timestamp":" 947590991144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590991794","data":{"timestamp":" 947590991794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIGUSE"," userResponse":" NIGUSE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590992433","data":{"timestamp":" 947590992432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590993012","data":{"timestamp":" 947590993012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" VIDONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590993691","data":{"timestamp":" 947590993690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKO"," userResponse":" VYAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590995948","data":{"timestamp":" 947590995948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590996772","data":{"timestamp":" 947590996772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" START_HERI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590997472","data":{"timestamp":" 947590997472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590997877","data":{"timestamp":" 947590997876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFE"," userResponse":" NIFE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947590999181","data":{"timestamp":" 947590999181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591000283","data":{"timestamp":" 947591000283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIGUSE"," userResponse":" NIGUSE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591001403","data":{"timestamp":" 947591001403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VYAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591003826","data":{"timestamp":" 947591003826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591003844","data":{"timestamp":" 947591003843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDONDA"," userResponse":" VIDONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591005542","data":{"timestamp":" 947591005541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Heri nife kuliko niguse vile vidonda vyako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKO"," userResponse":" VYAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591007287","data":{"timestamp":" 947591007287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591008117","data":{"timestamp":" 947591008116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591009400","data":{"timestamp":" 947591009399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMYA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591010100","data":{"timestamp":" 947591010099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591011120","data":{"timestamp":" 947591011120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591011790","data":{"timestamp":" 947591011790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591012380","data":{"timestamp":" 947591012379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJEMA"," userResponse":" NJEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591013984","data":{"timestamp":" 947591013983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591015040","data":{"timestamp":" 947591015040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" VYAKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591018178","data":{"timestamp":" 947591018177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591019969","data":{"timestamp":" 947591019968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMYA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591021274","data":{"timestamp":" 947591021273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591022959","data":{"timestamp":" 947591022959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAKIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591023472","data":{"timestamp":" 947591023472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591024501","data":{"timestamp":" 947591024501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591026233","data":{"timestamp":" 947591026233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591027007","data":{"timestamp":" 947591027007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule mwanamke alikimya na kumtakia safari njema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJEMA"," userResponse":" NJEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591029751","data":{"timestamp":" 947591029751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591030962","data":{"timestamp":" 947591030961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591031923","data":{"timestamp":" 947591031923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591032855","data":{"timestamp":" 947591032855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKA"," userResponse":" AKAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591033519","data":{"timestamp":" 947591033519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591034531","data":{"timestamp":" 947591034530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591035452","data":{"timestamp":" 947591035451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JONGOO"," userResponse":" JONGOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591036718","data":{"timestamp":" 947591036718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591037729","data":{"timestamp":" 947591037728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABUU"," userResponse":" MABUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591038463","data":{"timestamp":" 947591038462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591039095","data":{"timestamp":" 947591039095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591039970","data":{"timestamp":" 947591039969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591043284","data":{"timestamp":" 947591043283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBUYA"," userResponse":" NAMBUYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591044480","data":{"timestamp":" 947591044479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591047059","data":{"timestamp":" 947591047058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" MABUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591048845","data":{"timestamp":" 947591048844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591052235","data":{"timestamp":" 947591052234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591053760","data":{"timestamp":" 947591053759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591057387","data":{"timestamp":" 947591057387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKA"," userResponse":" AKAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591058829","data":{"timestamp":" 947591058828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591060308","data":{"timestamp":" 947591060308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591062131","data":{"timestamp":" 947591062131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591065131","data":{"timestamp":" 947591065130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591066110","data":{"timestamp":" 947591066110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591067981","data":{"timestamp":" 947591067981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591069355","data":{"timestamp":" 947591069354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JONGOO"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591070302","data":{"timestamp":" 947591070301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JONGOO"," userResponse":" JONGOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591071685","data":{"timestamp":" 947591071685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591075311","data":{"timestamp":" 947591075311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MABUU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591076866","data":{"timestamp":" 947591076866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABUU"," userResponse":" MABUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591077676","data":{"timestamp":" 947591077676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591080561","data":{"timestamp":" 947591080561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591085311","data":{"timestamp":" 947591085311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" START_WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591087103","data":{"timestamp":" 947591087103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nambuya alitembea hadi akafika mahali walipokuwa jongoo nyoka mabuu na wadudu wengine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591089139","data":{"timestamp":" 947591089139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591090611","data":{"timestamp":" 947591090610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHOKA"," userResponse":" AMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591091248","data":{"timestamp":" 947591091248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591092567","data":{"timestamp":" 947591092567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDHOOFIKA"," userResponse":" KUDHOOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591093203","data":{"timestamp":" 947591093203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591093903","data":{"timestamp":" 947591093902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591094682","data":{"timestamp":" 947591094681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591097638","data":{"timestamp":" 947591097638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591098556","data":{"timestamp":" 947591098555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHOKA"," userResponse":" AMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591099157","data":{"timestamp":" 947591099157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591102053","data":{"timestamp":" 947591102052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUDHOOFIKA"," userResponse":" KUDHOOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591104238","data":{"timestamp":" 947591104237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591106262","data":{"timestamp":" 947591106262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591107357","data":{"timestamp":" 947591107357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amechoka na kudhoofika kwa kukosa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591109745","data":{"timestamp":" 947591109744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKETI"," userResponse":" ALIPOKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591110276","data":{"timestamp":" 947591110276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591111377","data":{"timestamp":" 947591111376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" KUPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591112592","data":{"timestamp":" 947591112590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591113069","data":{"timestamp":" 947591113068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591113911","data":{"timestamp":" 947591113910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591114811","data":{"timestamp":" 947591114810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" KUMUUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591117823","data":{"timestamp":" 947591117823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKETI"," userResponse":" ALIPOKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591117826","data":{"timestamp":" 947591117826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591119849","data":{"timestamp":" 947591119848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591121389","data":{"timestamp":" 947591121389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591123123","data":{"timestamp":" 947591123122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591124275","data":{"timestamp":" 947591124275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" KUDHOOFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591125395","data":{"timestamp":" 947591125394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591126289","data":{"timestamp":" 947591126289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591127185","data":{"timestamp":" 947591127185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591128378","data":{"timestamp":" 947591128378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591129365","data":{"timestamp":" 947591129365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591130934","data":{"timestamp":" 947591130933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoketi chini kupumzika wadudu hawa walianza kumuuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591133707","data":{"timestamp":" 947591133706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591134686","data":{"timestamp":" 947591134686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591135746","data":{"timestamp":" 947591135745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" ALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591136566","data":{"timestamp":" 947591136565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591137043","data":{"timestamp":" 947591137042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591137631","data":{"timestamp":" 947591137630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591141421","data":{"timestamp":" 947591141421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591143305","data":{"timestamp":" 947591143305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591144754","data":{"timestamp":" 947591144754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMKUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591145919","data":{"timestamp":" 947591145918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" ALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591146904","data":{"timestamp":" 947591146903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591149330","data":{"timestamp":" 947591149329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591149642","data":{"timestamp":" 947591149642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591151553","data":{"timestamp":" 947591151553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani Nelima alimkuta mwanamke yule yule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591154163","data":{"timestamp":" 947591154162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591154902","data":{"timestamp":" 947591154901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591155905","data":{"timestamp":" 947591155904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591156658","data":{"timestamp":" 947591156657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591157448","data":{"timestamp":" 947591157447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591158307","data":{"timestamp":" 947591158306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591158402","data":{"timestamp":" 947591158401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591159168","data":{"timestamp":" 947591159167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591160490","data":{"timestamp":" 947591160489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" KUKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591161010","data":{"timestamp":" 947591161009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591161662","data":{"timestamp":" 947591161662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591162446","data":{"timestamp":" 947591162445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AANZE"," userResponse":" AANZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591163238","data":{"timestamp":" 947591163238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591163749","data":{"timestamp":" 947591163749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591166155","data":{"timestamp":" 947591166155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591168055","data":{"timestamp":" 947591168055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591169859","data":{"timestamp":" 947591169859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591171245","data":{"timestamp":" 947591171245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591173028","data":{"timestamp":" 947591173028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591174540","data":{"timestamp":" 947591174540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NETASILE"," userResponse":" NETASILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591176558","data":{"timestamp":" 947591176558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591178042","data":{"timestamp":" 947591178042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591179512","data":{"timestamp":" 947591179512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BINADAMU"," userResponse":" BINADAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591180572","data":{"timestamp":" 947591180571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591181005","data":{"timestamp":" 947591181005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591182356","data":{"timestamp":" 947591182356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591184319","data":{"timestamp":" 947591184319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591186081","data":{"timestamp":" 947591186080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUTANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591187155","data":{"timestamp":" 947591187155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591190249","data":{"timestamp":" 947591190248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591190828","data":{"timestamp":" 947591190828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AANZE"," userResponse":" AANZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591190834","data":{"timestamp":" 947591190834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591191446","data":{"timestamp":" 947591191446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kumwona Netasile kwani alikuwa binadamu wa kwanza kukutana naye tangu aanze safari yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591193561","data":{"timestamp":" 947591193560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591194621","data":{"timestamp":" 947591194620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591194867","data":{"timestamp":" 947591194867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591195748","data":{"timestamp":" 947591195747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591196529","data":{"timestamp":" 947591196528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591197552","data":{"timestamp":" 947591197552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591197770","data":{"timestamp":" 947591197769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591200032","data":{"timestamp":" 947591200032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591201320","data":{"timestamp":" 947591201320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591202438","data":{"timestamp":" 947591202438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591203506","data":{"timestamp":" 947591203506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591205179","data":{"timestamp":" 947591205179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" START_MASWALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591206923","data":{"timestamp":" 947591206922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591209298","data":{"timestamp":" 947591209298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591209394","data":{"timestamp":" 947591209394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke alimwita na kumuuliza maswali yale yale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591211990","data":{"timestamp":" 947591211989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591213181","data":{"timestamp":" 947591213181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" ALIKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591214112","data":{"timestamp":" 947591214111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591214803","data":{"timestamp":" 947591214802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591215453","data":{"timestamp":" 947591215452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591217413","data":{"timestamp":" 947591217413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591218525","data":{"timestamp":" 947591218525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591219947","data":{"timestamp":" 947591219946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591221770","data":{"timestamp":" 947591221769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591223447","data":{"timestamp":" 947591223446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591225255","data":{"timestamp":" 947591225254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUMPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591226567","data":{"timestamp":" 947591226567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591226758","data":{"timestamp":" 947591226757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alikubali kumpeleka nyumbani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591228985","data":{"timestamp":" 947591228984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFANYA"," userResponse":" UMEFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591229491","data":{"timestamp":" 947591229490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591229988","data":{"timestamp":" 947591229988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591230898","data":{"timestamp":" 947591230897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEMEKOSA"," userResponse":" WEMEKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591231688","data":{"timestamp":" 947591231688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591232929","data":{"timestamp":" 947591232928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591233829","data":{"timestamp":" 947591233829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591237669","data":{"timestamp":" 947591237669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEFANYA"," userResponse":" UMEFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591238055","data":{"timestamp":" 947591238055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591239479","data":{"timestamp":" 947591239478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591240422","data":{"timestamp":" 947591240422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WEMEKOSA"," userResponse":" START_WEMEKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591242313","data":{"timestamp":" 947591242312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEMEKOSA"," userResponse":" WEMEKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591243502","data":{"timestamp":" 947591243502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591245402","data":{"timestamp":" 947591245402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591247695","data":{"timestamp":" 947591247695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umefanya kile wengi wemekosa kufanya mwanamke alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591249723","data":{"timestamp":" 947591249722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591250433","data":{"timestamp":" 947591250432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591251364","data":{"timestamp":" 947591251364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJITI"," userResponse":" KIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591251834","data":{"timestamp":" 947591251833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591252724","data":{"timestamp":" 947591252723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591253384","data":{"timestamp":" 947591253383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARUDI"," userResponse":" ARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591254235","data":{"timestamp":" 947591254234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591255066","data":{"timestamp":" 947591255065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591255957","data":{"timestamp":" 947591255957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUTA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591256711","data":{"timestamp":" 947591256710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591257435","data":{"timestamp":" 947591257434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591258835","data":{"timestamp":" 947591258834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOTAKA"," userResponse":" ALICHOTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591262082","data":{"timestamp":" 947591262082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ARUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591263208","data":{"timestamp":" 947591263208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591264102","data":{"timestamp":" 947591264102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591265112","data":{"timestamp":" 947591265112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJITI"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591266885","data":{"timestamp":" 947591266885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIJITI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591268458","data":{"timestamp":" 947591268458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJITI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591269721","data":{"timestamp":" 947591269721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591270630","data":{"timestamp":" 947591270629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591273944","data":{"timestamp":" 947591273943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARUDI"," userResponse":" ARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591275352","data":{"timestamp":" 947591275352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591279306","data":{"timestamp":" 947591279306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591281013","data":{"timestamp":" 947591281013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591282398","data":{"timestamp":" 947591282398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" KIJITI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591283709","data":{"timestamp":" 947591283709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591284939","data":{"timestamp":" 947591284939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUTA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591285324","data":{"timestamp":" 947591285324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591286533","data":{"timestamp":" 947591286532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591289318","data":{"timestamp":" 947591289318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591290213","data":{"timestamp":" 947591290213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOTAKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591291880","data":{"timestamp":" 947591291880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimpa Nelima kijiti na kumwambia arudi nyumbani ambako angekuta kila kitu alichotaka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOTAKA"," userResponse":" ALICHOTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591294380","data":{"timestamp":" 947591294380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591295910","data":{"timestamp":" 947591295910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" ALIMSHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591296701","data":{"timestamp":" 947591296700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591297120","data":{"timestamp":" 947591297119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591297859","data":{"timestamp":" 947591297858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591300089","data":{"timestamp":" 947591300088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591301311","data":{"timestamp":" 947591301311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" ALIMSHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591302104","data":{"timestamp":" 947591302104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591302613","data":{"timestamp":" 947591302612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591303407","data":{"timestamp":" 947591303407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nelima alimshukuru mwanamke huyo mkongwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGWE"," userResponse":" MKONGWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591306092","data":{"timestamp":" 947591306091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591306913","data":{"timestamp":" 947591306912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591307438","data":{"timestamp":" 947591307437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591308148","data":{"timestamp":" 947591308147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591308735","data":{"timestamp":" 947591308734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591309406","data":{"timestamp":" 947591309404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591310542","data":{"timestamp":" 947591310541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591311543","data":{"timestamp":" 947591311543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591312045","data":{"timestamp":" 947591312044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591312651","data":{"timestamp":" 947591312650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591312830","data":{"timestamp":" 947591312830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591313477","data":{"timestamp":" 947591313476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591314530","data":{"timestamp":" 947591314529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGI"," userResponse":" KINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591320965","data":{"timestamp":" 947591320965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591322208","data":{"timestamp":" 947591322208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591324048","data":{"timestamp":" 947591324047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591325904","data":{"timestamp":" 947591325904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591327126","data":{"timestamp":" 947591327126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591328827","data":{"timestamp":" 947591328826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591329775","data":{"timestamp":" 947591329775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591330115","data":{"timestamp":" 947591330114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591332023","data":{"timestamp":" 947591332023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591333642","data":{"timestamp":" 947591333642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591335244","data":{"timestamp":" 947591335244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591336901","data":{"timestamp":" 947591336900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591338523","data":{"timestamp":" 947591338522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591338693","data":{"timestamp":" 947591338693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIMSHUKURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591340412","data":{"timestamp":" 947591340412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591341688","data":{"timestamp":" 947591341688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591342465","data":{"timestamp":" 947591342465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591343602","data":{"timestamp":" 947591343602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591345351","data":{"timestamp":" 947591345351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591347357","data":{"timestamp":" 947591347357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591349775","data":{"timestamp":" 947591349775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591351883","data":{"timestamp":" 947591351883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591354250","data":{"timestamp":" 947591354249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591357374","data":{"timestamp":" 947591357374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591360908","data":{"timestamp":" 947591360908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani na kupata nyumba mpya iliyojaa kila kitu pamoja na chakula kingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591362847","data":{"timestamp":" 947591362847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWA"," userResponse":" AKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591363799","data":{"timestamp":" 947591363799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591364560","data":{"timestamp":" 947591364559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591365439","data":{"timestamp":" 947591365438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591366217","data":{"timestamp":" 947591366217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHINI"," userResponse":" NCHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591368153","data":{"timestamp":" 947591368152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWA"," userResponse":" AKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591369216","data":{"timestamp":" 947591369216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591369722","data":{"timestamp":" 947591369722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591371112","data":{"timestamp":" 947591371112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591371751","data":{"timestamp":" 947591371751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akawa mwanamke tajiri zaidi nchini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHINI"," userResponse":" NCHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591374776","data":{"timestamp":" 947591374775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591376455","data":{"timestamp":" 947591376455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," userResponse":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591377544","data":{"timestamp":" 947591377543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUMPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591378534","data":{"timestamp":" 947591378533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591380936","data":{"timestamp":" 947591380935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591382418","data":{"timestamp":" 947591382418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," userResponse":" ALIOMBOLEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591383326","data":{"timestamp":" 947591383326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUMPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591384026","data":{"timestamp":" 947591384026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini aliomboleza kumpoteza dadake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591386282","data":{"timestamp":" 947591386282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591387852","data":{"timestamp":" 947591387851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYESIKIA"," userResponse":" ASIYESIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591389043","data":{"timestamp":" 947591389042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591390284","data":{"timestamp":" 947591390284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIA"," userResponse":" ALIISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591390863","data":{"timestamp":" 947591390863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591390980","data":{"timestamp":" 947591390980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591391701","data":{"timestamp":" 947591391700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" KINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591391970","data":{"timestamp":" 947591391968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591392688","data":{"timestamp":" 947591392687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591395769","data":{"timestamp":" 947591395768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591397859","data":{"timestamp":" 947591397858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYESIKIA"," userResponse":" START_ASIYESIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591399798","data":{"timestamp":" 947591399798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYESIKIA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591401833","data":{"timestamp":" 947591401833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYESIKIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591403091","data":{"timestamp":" 947591403090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USHAURI"," userResponse":" USHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591404313","data":{"timestamp":" 947591404313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIA"," userResponse":" START_ALIISHIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591405266","data":{"timestamp":" 947591405266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIA"," userResponse":" KINYWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591407177","data":{"timestamp":" 947591407176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591408256","data":{"timestamp":" 947591408256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591409471","data":{"timestamp":" 947591409470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591410433","data":{"timestamp":" 947591410433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591410937","data":{"timestamp":" 947591410937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591412015","data":{"timestamp":" 947591412014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591413529","data":{"timestamp":" 947591413529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591414208","data":{"timestamp":" 947591414207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591414723","data":{"timestamp":" 947591414722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591416755","data":{"timestamp":" 947591416754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591416882","data":{"timestamp":" 947591416882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591426280","data":{"timestamp":" 947591426280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" c82a6285-e5c1-4e92-9e83-d34d9a8c810d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alisema Asiyesikia ushauri aliishia ndani ya kinywa cha ndovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591439437","data":{"timestamp":" 947591439437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tabasamu_kumfanya-tabasamu-akamwona"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tabasamu"," userResponse":" tabasamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591446488","data":{"timestamp":" 947591446488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_samahani_nitakufa-mbinguni-samahani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" samahani"," userResponse":" samahani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591453324","data":{"timestamp":" 947591453324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alimwona_alimwona-mlangoni-kusubiri"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alimwona"," userResponse":" alimwona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591458728","data":{"timestamp":" 947591458728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_blanketi_kitambaa-blanketi-walihisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" blanketi"," userResponse":" blanketi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591464268","data":{"timestamp":" 947591464268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusubiri_polepole-kusubiri-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusubiri"," userResponse":" kusubiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591471103","data":{"timestamp":" 947591471103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alicheza_waliimba-mwekundu-alicheza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alicheza"," userResponse":" alicheza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591477538","data":{"timestamp":" 947591477538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alishika_chunguni-pilipili-alishika"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alishika"," userResponse":" alishika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591484784","data":{"timestamp":" 947591484783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kusafiri_mwanangu-kusafiri-alisikia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kusafiri"," userResponse":" kusafiri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591489814","data":{"timestamp":" 947591489814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nonkungu_nonkungu-hakuwahi-alikataa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nonkungu"," userResponse":" nonkungu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591496052","data":{"timestamp":" 947591496052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninaweza"," userResponse":" ninaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591501850","data":{"timestamp":" 947591501849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 99089657-aa6a-4db8-8134-9324e7d4ed96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ninaweza_shambani-hakuwahi-ninaweza"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591518988","data":{"timestamp":" 947591518988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vibonyeo_mbinguni-vibonyeo-mtonyama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vibonyeo"," userResponse":" vibonyeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591525568","data":{"timestamp":" 947591525568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sitawahi_alifuata-sitawahi-mkongojo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sitawahi"," userResponse":" sitawahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591530522","data":{"timestamp":" 947591530522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walianza_walianza-sakafuni-alipenda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walianza"," userResponse":" walianza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591540072","data":{"timestamp":" 947591540072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ikitokea_ikitokea-kuwapata-hakikuwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ikitokea"," userResponse":" ikitokea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591547839","data":{"timestamp":" 947591547839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" halikuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591552860","data":{"timestamp":" 947591552860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_konokono_konokono-shughuli-kimbieni"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" konokono"," userResponse":" konokono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591562314","data":{"timestamp":" 947591562314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nililala_nililala-lilisema-chochote"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nililala"," userResponse":" nililala"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591573338","data":{"timestamp":" 947591573338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tunaweza_sawasawa-tunaweza-kikaango"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tunaweza"," userResponse":" tunaweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591579357","data":{"timestamp":" 947591579357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ninanuka_ninanuka-shingoni-nitakufa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ninanuka"," userResponse":" ninanuka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591591277","data":{"timestamp":" 947591591277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hakuwahi_hakuwahi-waliishi-akakataa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hakuwahi"," userResponse":" hakuwahi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591597085","data":{"timestamp":" 947591597085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" ebf8d905-e9fe-4dda-b431-83ef7e753d11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_hakuwahi_hakuwahi-waliishi-akakataa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591612735","data":{"timestamp":" 947591612734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591617625","data":{"timestamp":" 947591617624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591619978","data":{"timestamp":" 947591619978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591622132","data":{"timestamp":" 947591622131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591626765","data":{"timestamp":" 947591626764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591629178","data":{"timestamp":" 947591629178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591631551","data":{"timestamp":" 947591631551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591633419","data":{"timestamp":" 947591633418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591635853","data":{"timestamp":" 947591635853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591637590","data":{"timestamp":" 947591637589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591638278","data":{"timestamp":" 947591638277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591638514","data":{"timestamp":" 947591638513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591639243","data":{"timestamp":" 947591639242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591640552","data":{"timestamp":" 947591640551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591641211","data":{"timestamp":" 947591641210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591642111","data":{"timestamp":" 947591642111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591643035","data":{"timestamp":" 947591643035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591643754","data":{"timestamp":" 947591643753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591648025","data":{"timestamp":" 947591648025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591651107","data":{"timestamp":" 947591651106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591653661","data":{"timestamp":" 947591653660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591656159","data":{"timestamp":" 947591656158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591658179","data":{"timestamp":" 947591658178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591660735","data":{"timestamp":" 947591660735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591662862","data":{"timestamp":" 947591662862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591665430","data":{"timestamp":" 947591665429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591667747","data":{"timestamp":" 947591667747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591669742","data":{"timestamp":" 947591669741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591670338","data":{"timestamp":" 947591670338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591670852","data":{"timestamp":" 947591670851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591671575","data":{"timestamp":" 947591671575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591672419","data":{"timestamp":" 947591672419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591672822","data":{"timestamp":" 947591672822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591673606","data":{"timestamp":" 947591673606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591674250","data":{"timestamp":" 947591674249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591675262","data":{"timestamp":" 947591675261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591679571","data":{"timestamp":" 947591679570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591681943","data":{"timestamp":" 947591681942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591683874","data":{"timestamp":" 947591683873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591686860","data":{"timestamp":" 947591686860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591688965","data":{"timestamp":" 947591688964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591690820","data":{"timestamp":" 947591690820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591692523","data":{"timestamp":" 947591692523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591692621","data":{"timestamp":" 947591692621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" efb147d2-698b-4fdd-b2d6-66b7361b1f86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591718639","data":{"timestamp":" 947591718639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_haidhuru_kiangazi_nahitaji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591726092","data":{"timestamp":" 947591726091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_haidhuru_kiangazi_nahitaji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591732766","data":{"timestamp":" 947591732766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kushtaki_akachoma_walijaze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591739379","data":{"timestamp":" 947591739378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwanamke_kufikiri_wenzangu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591746013","data":{"timestamp":" 947591746013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nausikia_halikuwa_aliupata"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591752665","data":{"timestamp":" 947591752665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_omusiani_nitapata_utapotea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591760117","data":{"timestamp":" 947591760116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_omusiani_nitapata_utapotea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591766758","data":{"timestamp":" 947591766758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_msichana_michache_kutimiza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591773361","data":{"timestamp":" 947591773361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_amepakwa_sikuwahi_demazane"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591780000","data":{"timestamp":" 947591780000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ulidunda_nikiugua_likiitwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591786626","data":{"timestamp":" 947591786626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kunibeba_kijijini_angeenda"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591793248","data":{"timestamp":" 947591793248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_aliongea_kuanguka_msisimko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.8.noShow.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591805344","data":{"timestamp":" 947591805343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" e7f7dc92-6d56-4fe3-a24c-c66e09c700b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.8.noShow.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_aliongea_kuanguka_msisimko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591820263","data":{"timestamp":" 947591820262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHAYANGA"," userResponse":" KHAYANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591821099","data":{"timestamp":" 947591821099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591821375","data":{"timestamp":" 947591821374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591822034","data":{"timestamp":" 947591822033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591822590","data":{"timestamp":" 947591822589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591822886","data":{"timestamp":" 947591822885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591823641","data":{"timestamp":" 947591823641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591824502","data":{"timestamp":" 947591824501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591825082","data":{"timestamp":" 947591825082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591826353","data":{"timestamp":" 947591826352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFARIKI"," userResponse":" WALIPOFARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591827088","data":{"timestamp":" 947591827087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591827338","data":{"timestamp":" 947591827338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591827937","data":{"timestamp":" 947591827937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591828129","data":{"timestamp":" 947591828128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591828750","data":{"timestamp":" 947591828750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591829445","data":{"timestamp":" 947591829444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591836869","data":{"timestamp":" 947591836869"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHAYANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591839713","data":{"timestamp":" 947591839712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591841675","data":{"timestamp":" 947591841675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591844085","data":{"timestamp":" 947591844085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591846058","data":{"timestamp":" 947591846057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591848080","data":{"timestamp":" 947591848079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591850355","data":{"timestamp":" 947591850355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591852673","data":{"timestamp":" 947591852673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591854520","data":{"timestamp":" 947591854520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591857231","data":{"timestamp":" 947591857231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFARIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591859476","data":{"timestamp":" 947591859476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591861623","data":{"timestamp":" 947591861623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591863926","data":{"timestamp":" 947591863925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591866189","data":{"timestamp":" 947591866189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591868332","data":{"timestamp":" 947591868332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591869609","data":{"timestamp":" 947591869609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga aliishi na wazazi wake kwa furaha hadi siku walipofariki akiwa na umri wa miaka kumi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591872586","data":{"timestamp":" 947591872586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHAYANGA"," userResponse":" KHAYANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591873974","data":{"timestamp":" 947591873973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ALICHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591874634","data":{"timestamp":" 947591874633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591875563","data":{"timestamp":" 947591875562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUNZWA"," userResponse":" KUTUNZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591876053","data":{"timestamp":" 947591876052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591876489","data":{"timestamp":" 947591876488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591877088","data":{"timestamp":" 947591877087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591877366","data":{"timestamp":" 947591877365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591878057","data":{"timestamp":" 947591878056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKOO"," userResponse":" UKOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591878712","data":{"timestamp":" 947591878712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591879652","data":{"timestamp":" 947591879652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591880251","data":{"timestamp":" 947591880251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROSA"," userResponse":" ROSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591882461","data":{"timestamp":" 947591882461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KHAYANGA"," userResponse":" KHAYANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591883956","data":{"timestamp":" 947591883956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" KUTUNZWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591884589","data":{"timestamp":" 947591884589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591884780","data":{"timestamp":" 947591884780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" KUTUNZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591900535","data":{"timestamp":" 947591900534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 70671269-2f38-4a88-83cc-e5f20ce07338"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Khayanga alichukuliwa ili kutunzwa na mama mmoja wa ukoo wake aliyeitwa Rosa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591916761","data":{"timestamp":" 947591916761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591917827","data":{"timestamp":" 947591917827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591922537","data":{"timestamp":" 947591922537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" halikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591923598","data":{"timestamp":" 947591923598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" halikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591927089","data":{"timestamp":" 947591927088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwaita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAITA"," userResponse":" ALIWAITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591928145","data":{"timestamp":" 947591928144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwaita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAITA"," userResponse":" ALIWAITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591931761","data":{"timestamp":" 947591931760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591932806","data":{"timestamp":" 947591932806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591936093","data":{"timestamp":" 947591936092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591937157","data":{"timestamp":" 947591937156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591942388","data":{"timestamp":" 947591942387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591943447","data":{"timestamp":" 947591943446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591947356","data":{"timestamp":" 947591947355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" matatizo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591948414","data":{"timestamp":" 947591948414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" matatizo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591949035","data":{"timestamp":" 947591949034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" matatizo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591949137","data":{"timestamp":" 947591949137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f97b9a09-2e13-4df3-b64a-b98fcba2c328"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" matatizo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591969303","data":{"timestamp":" 947591969302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591969946","data":{"timestamp":" 947591969945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591970204","data":{"timestamp":" 947591970203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591970772","data":{"timestamp":" 947591970771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591971932","data":{"timestamp":" 947591971932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591972699","data":{"timestamp":" 947591972698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591974119","data":{"timestamp":" 947591974119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591975020","data":{"timestamp":" 947591975019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591975663","data":{"timestamp":" 947591975662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591976603","data":{"timestamp":" 947591976602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591977253","data":{"timestamp":" 947591977253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591979650","data":{"timestamp":" 947591979650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591979902","data":{"timestamp":" 947591979902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591980844","data":{"timestamp":" 947591980843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591981734","data":{"timestamp":" 947591981733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591982584","data":{"timestamp":" 947591982584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591983492","data":{"timestamp":" 947591983491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591986271","data":{"timestamp":" 947591986271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591986706","data":{"timestamp":" 947591986705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591987415","data":{"timestamp":" 947591987414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591988474","data":{"timestamp":" 947591988473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591989415","data":{"timestamp":" 947591989414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591990246","data":{"timestamp":" 947591990245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591991198","data":{"timestamp":" 947591991197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591992828","data":{"timestamp":" 947591992827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591993037","data":{"timestamp":" 947591993036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591993900","data":{"timestamp":" 947591993900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591994612","data":{"timestamp":" 947591994612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591994924","data":{"timestamp":" 947591994923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591995811","data":{"timestamp":" 947591995809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591996881","data":{"timestamp":" 947591996880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947591999944","data":{"timestamp":" 947591999943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592000564","data":{"timestamp":" 947592000564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592001675","data":{"timestamp":" 947592001675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592002827","data":{"timestamp":" 947592002826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592003187","data":{"timestamp":" 947592003186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592004070","data":{"timestamp":" 947592004069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592005314","data":{"timestamp":" 947592005313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592006157","data":{"timestamp":" 947592006156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592008793","data":{"timestamp":" 947592008791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592009692","data":{"timestamp":" 947592009692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592010277","data":{"timestamp":" 947592010276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592010532","data":{"timestamp":" 947592010531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592011248","data":{"timestamp":" 947592011248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592012053","data":{"timestamp":" 947592012053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592014638","data":{"timestamp":" 947592014637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592015641","data":{"timestamp":" 947592015640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592016118","data":{"timestamp":" 947592016117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592016381","data":{"timestamp":" 947592016380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592017172","data":{"timestamp":" 947592017171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592018472","data":{"timestamp":" 947592018471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592018787","data":{"timestamp":" 947592018787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592020011","data":{"timestamp":" 947592020011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMUKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592020937","data":{"timestamp":" 947592020936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592021601","data":{"timestamp":" 947592021601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592021855","data":{"timestamp":" 947592021855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592022724","data":{"timestamp":" 947592022722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592023270","data":{"timestamp":" 947592023269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592023857","data":{"timestamp":" 947592023856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592024429","data":{"timestamp":" 947592024428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592027205","data":{"timestamp":" 947592027204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592028469","data":{"timestamp":" 947592028469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592029496","data":{"timestamp":" 947592029495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592030857","data":{"timestamp":" 947592030856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAZIJAIVA"," userResponse":" HAZIJAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592031903","data":{"timestamp":" 947592031903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592032445","data":{"timestamp":" 947592032444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592033608","data":{"timestamp":" 947592033607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592035069","data":{"timestamp":" 947592035068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592036216","data":{"timestamp":" 947592036215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRI"," userResponse":" SUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592036763","data":{"timestamp":" 947592036763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592037726","data":{"timestamp":" 947592037725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwambia bado hazijaiva lakini hivi karibuni zitaiva subiri tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592040300","data":{"timestamp":" 947592040299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592041283","data":{"timestamp":" 947592041282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592041596","data":{"timestamp":" 947592041595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592042371","data":{"timestamp":" 947592042370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592043742","data":{"timestamp":" 947592043742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592044416","data":{"timestamp":" 947592044416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592044843","data":{"timestamp":" 947592044843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592045696","data":{"timestamp":" 947592045696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592046739","data":{"timestamp":" 947592046738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592047222","data":{"timestamp":" 947592047222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592048175","data":{"timestamp":" 947592048175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJUKUMU"," userResponse":" MAJUKUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592048377","data":{"timestamp":" 947592048376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592049162","data":{"timestamp":" 947592049161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alisema kwa haraka ningependa kufanya hivyo Sungura lakini nina majukumu ya kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592051807","data":{"timestamp":" 947592051806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592052820","data":{"timestamp":" 947592052819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592053791","data":{"timestamp":" 947592053791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANGESUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592055015","data":{"timestamp":" 947592055014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592055662","data":{"timestamp":" 947592055661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592056815","data":{"timestamp":" 947592056815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592057649","data":{"timestamp":" 947592057648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMPA"," userResponse":" ANGEMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592058407","data":{"timestamp":" 947592058406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592058575","data":{"timestamp":" 947592058575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592059347","data":{"timestamp":" 947592059346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alijua angesubiri bila shaka Sungura angempa kazi za kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592062568","data":{"timestamp":" 947592062567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592063856","data":{"timestamp":" 947592063855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWABIA"," userResponse":" AKAMWABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592064705","data":{"timestamp":" 947592064705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592066906","data":{"timestamp":" 947592066905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITASOKOTA"," userResponse":" NITASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592067785","data":{"timestamp":" 947592067785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592069027","data":{"timestamp":" 947592069027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUNGE"," userResponse":" NIFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592069719","data":{"timestamp":" 947592069718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592070285","data":{"timestamp":" 947592070285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592070926","data":{"timestamp":" 947592070925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592071962","data":{"timestamp":" 947592071962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592072363","data":{"timestamp":" 947592072362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592073097","data":{"timestamp":" 947592073096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592073595","data":{"timestamp":" 947592073595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592074059","data":{"timestamp":" 947592074059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592074679","data":{"timestamp":" 947592074679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592077023","data":{"timestamp":" 947592077022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592078716","data":{"timestamp":" 947592078716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," userResponse":" ZITAKAPOIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592079877","data":{"timestamp":" 947592079876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUTA"," userResponse":" VUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592080654","data":{"timestamp":" 947592080653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592081126","data":{"timestamp":" 947592081125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592082205","data":{"timestamp":" 947592082205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592082772","data":{"timestamp":" 947592082772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mboga zitakapoiva vuta utando na nitakimbia nije."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJE"," userResponse":" NIJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592085455","data":{"timestamp":" 947592085454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592086373","data":{"timestamp":" 947592086373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592087094","data":{"timestamp":" 947592087094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592087282","data":{"timestamp":" 947592087281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592087809","data":{"timestamp":" 947592087808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592088542","data":{"timestamp":" 947592088541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592089111","data":{"timestamp":" 947592089111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona hilo ni wazo zuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592092039","data":{"timestamp":" 947592092038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592092665","data":{"timestamp":" 947592092665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592095924","data":{"timestamp":" 947592095924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592097327","data":{"timestamp":" 947592097325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592097616","data":{"timestamp":" 947592097615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592098488","data":{"timestamp":" 947592098488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592099761","data":{"timestamp":" 947592099760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592100642","data":{"timestamp":" 947592100642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592100741","data":{"timestamp":" 947592100741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592101090","data":{"timestamp":" 947592101090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592102143","data":{"timestamp":" 947592102143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSISIMKO"," userResponse":" MSISIMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592103095","data":{"timestamp":" 947592103095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592105086","data":{"timestamp":" 947592105085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592105940","data":{"timestamp":" 947592105939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592106046","data":{"timestamp":" 947592106046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592107043","data":{"timestamp":" 947592107042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592108516","data":{"timestamp":" 947592108516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592109582","data":{"timestamp":" 947592109582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592111148","data":{"timestamp":" 947592111147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPIKWA"," userResponse":" YANAPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592111703","data":{"timestamp":" 947592111702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592112459","data":{"timestamp":" 947592112458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Sungura njiani alinusa na kwa msisimko akasema nasikia harufu ya maharage maharage matamu yanapikwa kwenye chungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592115516","data":{"timestamp":" 947592115514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592116761","data":{"timestamp":" 947592116759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWITA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592117574","data":{"timestamp":" 947592117573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592118689","data":{"timestamp":" 947592118689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592119292","data":{"timestamp":" 947592119292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592120275","data":{"timestamp":" 947592120273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592121136","data":{"timestamp":" 947592121136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592122252","data":{"timestamp":" 947592122252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592123354","data":{"timestamp":" 947592123353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATAIVA"," userResponse":" YATAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592126015","data":{"timestamp":" 947592126014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592127036","data":{"timestamp":" 947592127036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592128736","data":{"timestamp":" 947592128735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592129377","data":{"timestamp":" 947592129376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592129785","data":{"timestamp":" 947592129785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592130611","data":{"timestamp":" 947592130611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akasema ningependa sana Baba Ngedere."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592133444","data":{"timestamp":" 947592133443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592134639","data":{"timestamp":" 947592134636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHAURI"," userResponse":" AKASHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592135252","data":{"timestamp":" 947592135251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592136101","data":{"timestamp":" 947592136100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592137394","data":{"timestamp":" 947592137394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATASOKOTA"," userResponse":" ATASOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592138276","data":{"timestamp":" 947592138275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592139402","data":{"timestamp":" 947592139401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592139890","data":{"timestamp":" 947592139890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592140491","data":{"timestamp":" 947592140490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592141364","data":{"timestamp":" 947592141364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592142017","data":{"timestamp":" 947592142017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592142679","data":{"timestamp":" 947592142679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592143201","data":{"timestamp":" 947592143201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592143957","data":{"timestamp":" 947592143956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592144447","data":{"timestamp":" 947592144446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592144989","data":{"timestamp":" 947592144988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592145986","data":{"timestamp":" 947592145986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUBWA"," userResponse":" KIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592146260","data":{"timestamp":" 947592146259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592147149","data":{"timestamp":" 947592147148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akashauri tena kwamba atasokota utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu kikubwa cha maharage."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592149222","data":{"timestamp":" 947592149221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592150079","data":{"timestamp":" 947592150079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592151021","data":{"timestamp":" 947592151020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592151660","data":{"timestamp":" 947592151660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592151889","data":{"timestamp":" 947592151888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592152829","data":{"timestamp":" 947592152828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592153986","data":{"timestamp":" 947592153985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592154536","data":{"timestamp":" 947592154535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592155338","data":{"timestamp":" 947592155338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592156132","data":{"timestamp":" 947592156132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592156720","data":{"timestamp":" 947592156719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592157570","data":{"timestamp":" 947592157570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592158453","data":{"timestamp":" 947592158452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592159307","data":{"timestamp":" 947592159307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592160024","data":{"timestamp":" 947592160024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592162030","data":{"timestamp":" 947592162029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592162587","data":{"timestamp":" 947592162586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592163580","data":{"timestamp":" 947592163580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592164267","data":{"timestamp":" 947592164267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hiyo wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592167554","data":{"timestamp":" 947592167554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592168935","data":{"timestamp":" 947592168934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592169184","data":{"timestamp":" 947592169184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592169587","data":{"timestamp":" 947592169586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592170430","data":{"timestamp":" 947592170429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGEDERE"," userResponse":" NGEDERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592171762","data":{"timestamp":" 947592171760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592173385","data":{"timestamp":" 947592173385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUSA"," userResponse":" ALINUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592173635","data":{"timestamp":" 947592173634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592174713","data":{"timestamp":" 947592174712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592176309","data":{"timestamp":" 947592176308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592177804","data":{"timestamp":" 947592177803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592178578","data":{"timestamp":" 947592178578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592178684","data":{"timestamp":" 947592178684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592179340","data":{"timestamp":" 947592179340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592180217","data":{"timestamp":" 947592180216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592182243","data":{"timestamp":" 947592182243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAMINI"," userResponse":" NAAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592182468","data":{"timestamp":" 947592182468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592183184","data":{"timestamp":" 947592183184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592184081","data":{"timestamp":" 947592184080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592184286","data":{"timestamp":" 947592184286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592185512","data":{"timestamp":" 947592185511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alipoondoka kwa Baba Ngedere njiani alinusa kwa furaha akasema nasikia harufu ya viazi vitamu naamini ni viazi vitamu na asali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592188137","data":{"timestamp":" 947592188137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592188541","data":{"timestamp":" 947592188541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592189225","data":{"timestamp":" 947592189225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592190133","data":{"timestamp":" 947592190133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWITA"," userResponse":" ALIMWITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592191148","data":{"timestamp":" 947592191148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592192334","data":{"timestamp":" 947592192334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592192999","data":{"timestamp":" 947592192999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592194174","data":{"timestamp":" 947592194174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEJAA"," userResponse":" KIMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592194808","data":{"timestamp":" 947592194808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592195624","data":{"timestamp":" 947592195623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592195769","data":{"timestamp":" 947592195769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592196783","data":{"timestamp":" 947592196783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592199127","data":{"timestamp":" 947592199127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592199632","data":{"timestamp":" 947592199632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592200459","data":{"timestamp":" 947592200459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njoo tule pamoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592203375","data":{"timestamp":" 947592203374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEPENDA"," userResponse":" NINGEPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592204091","data":{"timestamp":" 947592204091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592204696","data":{"timestamp":" 947592204696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592205541","data":{"timestamp":" 947592205541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592206566","data":{"timestamp":" 947592206566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningependa kufanya hivyo Anansi akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592208725","data":{"timestamp":" 947592208725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592209158","data":{"timestamp":" 947592209158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592210158","data":{"timestamp":" 947592210158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592211303","data":{"timestamp":" 947592211302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592212454","data":{"timestamp":" 947592212453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHAURI"," userResponse":" ALISHAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592213229","data":{"timestamp":" 947592213229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592214714","data":{"timestamp":" 947592214714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASOKOTE"," userResponse":" ASOKOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592215630","data":{"timestamp":" 947592215629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592216945","data":{"timestamp":" 947592216944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFUNGE"," userResponse":" AFUNGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592217476","data":{"timestamp":" 947592217476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592218082","data":{"timestamp":" 947592218082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592218927","data":{"timestamp":" 947592218927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" MGUUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592219744","data":{"timestamp":" 947592219744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592220370","data":{"timestamp":" 947592220370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592220916","data":{"timestamp":" 947592220916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592221671","data":{"timestamp":" 947592221671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592222176","data":{"timestamp":" 947592222176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592222776","data":{"timestamp":" 947592222775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592222973","data":{"timestamp":" 947592222973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592223638","data":{"timestamp":" 947592223638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592224465","data":{"timestamp":" 947592224464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mara nyingine Anansi alishauri kwamba asokote utando afunge ncha moja mguuni kwake na ncha nyingine kwenye chungu cha viazi vitamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592227114","data":{"timestamp":" 947592227114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592227479","data":{"timestamp":" 947592227479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592228123","data":{"timestamp":" 947592228122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGURUWE"," userResponse":" NGURUWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592228897","data":{"timestamp":" 947592228896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONA"," userResponse":" AKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592229131","data":{"timestamp":" 947592229131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592229622","data":{"timestamp":" 947592229621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592230453","data":{"timestamp":" 947592230452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592231235","data":{"timestamp":" 947592231234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592232297","data":{"timestamp":" 947592232296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592232898","data":{"timestamp":" 947592232897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yake Nguruwe akaona ni wazo zuri na wakafanya hivyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592236244","data":{"timestamp":" 947592236243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592237002","data":{"timestamp":" 947592237001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592237976","data":{"timestamp":" 947592237975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592238840","data":{"timestamp":" 947592238840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592239885","data":{"timestamp":" 947592239885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592240369","data":{"timestamp":" 947592240369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592241450","data":{"timestamp":" 947592241449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592242622","data":{"timestamp":" 947592242621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592243966","data":{"timestamp":" 947592243965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEFUNGWA"," userResponse":" IMEFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592244310","data":{"timestamp":" 947592244310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592244984","data":{"timestamp":" 947592244984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592245268","data":{"timestamp":" 947592245268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592246306","data":{"timestamp":" 947592246305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati Anansi anafika mtoni miguu yake yote ilikuwa imefungwa kwa ncha za utando."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592249013","data":{"timestamp":" 947592249013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592250544","data":{"timestamp":" 947592250543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" AKAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592251759","data":{"timestamp":" 947592251758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592252066","data":{"timestamp":" 947592252066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592253088","data":{"timestamp":" 947592253088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIVUNO"," userResponse":" MAJIVUNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592254013","data":{"timestamp":" 947592254012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592254993","data":{"timestamp":" 947592254992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592255222","data":{"timestamp":" 947592255221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592255691","data":{"timestamp":" 947592255691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592256416","data":{"timestamp":" 947592256415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592256946","data":{"timestamp":" 947592256945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592258681","data":{"timestamp":" 947592258681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592259216","data":{"timestamp":" 947592259216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592260061","data":{"timestamp":" 947592260061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592260295","data":{"timestamp":" 947592260295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592261311","data":{"timestamp":" 947592261311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAIVA"," userResponse":" KITAIVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592262698","data":{"timestamp":" 947592262697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajisemea mwenyewe kwa majivuno hili lilikuwa ni wazo zuri sana najiuliza ni chungu kipi kitaiva kwanza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592264757","data":{"timestamp":" 947592264757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592265307","data":{"timestamp":" 947592265307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592266138","data":{"timestamp":" 947592266138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592267048","data":{"timestamp":" 947592267047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592267541","data":{"timestamp":" 947592267541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592269045","data":{"timestamp":" 947592269045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEVUTWA"," userResponse":" UMEVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592271595","data":{"timestamp":" 947592271595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592272071","data":{"timestamp":" 947592272071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AH"," userResponse":" AH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592273489","data":{"timestamp":" 947592273487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592273897","data":{"timestamp":" 947592273897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592274345","data":{"timestamp":" 947592274345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592274673","data":{"timestamp":" 947592274673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592275648","data":{"timestamp":" 947592275648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANDO"," userResponse":" UTANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592277023","data":{"timestamp":" 947592277022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592278089","data":{"timestamp":" 947592278088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592278815","data":{"timestamp":" 947592278814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592279045","data":{"timestamp":" 947592279044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592279818","data":{"timestamp":" 947592279818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592280089","data":{"timestamp":" 947592280088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592280706","data":{"timestamp":" 947592280706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592280929","data":{"timestamp":" 947592280928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592281835","data":{"timestamp":" 947592281834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akasema Ah hii ni ncha ya utando iliyofungwa kwenye chungu cha Sungura cha mboga za majani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592284835","data":{"timestamp":" 947592284834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592285410","data":{"timestamp":" 947592285410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUTO"," userResponse":" MVUTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592286244","data":{"timestamp":" 947592286244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592287167","data":{"timestamp":" 947592287166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592288098","data":{"timestamp":" 947592288097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592290848","data":{"timestamp":" 947592290848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592292021","data":{"timestamp":" 947592292021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592292545","data":{"timestamp":" 947592292545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANDE"," userResponse":" PANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592293430","data":{"timestamp":" 947592293430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592294353","data":{"timestamp":" 947592294353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592294988","data":{"timestamp":" 947592294988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592295682","data":{"timestamp":" 947592295682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi alivutwa pande tatu kwa mara moja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592297947","data":{"timestamp":" 947592297947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592299072","data":{"timestamp":" 947592299072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMANI"," userResponse":" JAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592300247","data":{"timestamp":" 947592300247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592301281","data":{"timestamp":" 947592301281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592302125","data":{"timestamp":" 947592302125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592302460","data":{"timestamp":" 947592302460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592303304","data":{"timestamp":" 947592303304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTWA"," userResponse":" KUVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592303559","data":{"timestamp":" 947592303559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592304083","data":{"timestamp":" 947592304083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592304278","data":{"timestamp":" 947592304278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592304873","data":{"timestamp":" 947592304873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Oh jamani Anansi alisema baada ya kuvutwa kwa mara ya nne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592307559","data":{"timestamp":" 947592307559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592308182","data":{"timestamp":" 947592308182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592308656","data":{"timestamp":" 947592308656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592309959","data":{"timestamp":" 947592309959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592310460","data":{"timestamp":" 947592310460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592310678","data":{"timestamp":" 947592310677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592311349","data":{"timestamp":" 947592311348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592312383","data":{"timestamp":" 947592312383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAVUTWA"," userResponse":" INAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592313078","data":{"timestamp":" 947592313078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592313283","data":{"timestamp":" 947592313283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592313919","data":{"timestamp":" 947592313918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592314793","data":{"timestamp":" 947592314793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592315048","data":{"timestamp":" 947592315048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592315763","data":{"timestamp":" 947592315763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592316559","data":{"timestamp":" 947592316559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592316825","data":{"timestamp":" 947592316825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592317551","data":{"timestamp":" 947592317551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo akasikia ncha ya tano inavutwa na ya sita na ya saba na ya nane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592320276","data":{"timestamp":" 947592320276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592321565","data":{"timestamp":" 947592321565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTWA"," userResponse":" ALIVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592322440","data":{"timestamp":" 947592322440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592322794","data":{"timestamp":" 947592322794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592323298","data":{"timestamp":" 947592323298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592324102","data":{"timestamp":" 947592324102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592324367","data":{"timestamp":" 947592324367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592326979","data":{"timestamp":" 947592326979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592327453","data":{"timestamp":" 947592327453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592328430","data":{"timestamp":" 947592328429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" AKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592328896","data":{"timestamp":" 947592328896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILE"," userResponse":" ZILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592329597","data":{"timestamp":" 947592329597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592330182","data":{"timestamp":" 947592330180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592330785","data":{"timestamp":" 947592330785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592331705","data":{"timestamp":" 947592331704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu akavuta zile ncha kwa wakati mmoja."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592334204","data":{"timestamp":" 947592334204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592334743","data":{"timestamp":" 947592334743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592336006","data":{"timestamp":" 947592336005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTWA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592336816","data":{"timestamp":" 947592336815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592338030","data":{"timestamp":" 947592338030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592338384","data":{"timestamp":" 947592338384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592339628","data":{"timestamp":" 947592339628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miguu yake ikavutwa ikawa myembamba na myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592342980","data":{"timestamp":" 947592342980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592344495","data":{"timestamp":" 947592344494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIRUSHA"," userResponse":" AKAJIRUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592345029","data":{"timestamp":" 947592345029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592345633","data":{"timestamp":" 947592345633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akajirusha haraka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592348412","data":{"timestamp":" 947592348412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592348999","data":{"timestamp":" 947592348999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANDO"," userResponse":" TANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592349563","data":{"timestamp":" 947592349563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592350877","data":{"timestamp":" 947592350877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," userResponse":" ZIMECHUKULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592351153","data":{"timestamp":" 947592351152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592352016","data":{"timestamp":" 947592352015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592353750","data":{"timestamp":" 947592353750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIVUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592355370","data":{"timestamp":" 947592355369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TARATIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592356033","data":{"timestamp":" 947592356033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592357668","data":{"timestamp":" 947592357667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMIVU"," userResponse":" MAUMIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592358732","data":{"timestamp":" 947592358732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592359277","data":{"timestamp":" 947592359276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592360151","data":{"timestamp":" 947592360151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati tando zote zimechukuliwa na maji alijivuta taratibu kwa maumivu hadi kwenye ufukwe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UFUKWE"," userResponse":" UFUKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592362612","data":{"timestamp":" 947592362611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592364266","data":{"timestamp":" 947592364266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAHEMA"," userResponse":" AKAHEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592365126","data":{"timestamp":" 947592365125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592366336","data":{"timestamp":" 947592366336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJONZI"," userResponse":" MAJONZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592367341","data":{"timestamp":" 947592367341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592368177","data":{"timestamp":" 947592368176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592369036","data":{"timestamp":" 947592369035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OH"," userResponse":" OH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592369834","data":{"timestamp":" 947592369834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592371072","data":{"timestamp":" 947592371071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGINE"," userResponse":" PENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592371705","data":{"timestamp":" 947592371705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592372777","data":{"timestamp":" 947592372777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592373421","data":{"timestamp":" 947592373421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592373999","data":{"timestamp":" 947592373999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592374724","data":{"timestamp":" 947592374724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi akahema kwa majonzi Oh mimi oh mimi pengine hili halikuwa wazo zuri kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592376918","data":{"timestamp":" 947592376918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592377577","data":{"timestamp":" 947592377576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592378183","data":{"timestamp":" 947592378182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592379576","data":{"timestamp":" 947592379576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592380768","data":{"timestamp":" 947592380767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592381539","data":{"timestamp":" 947592381538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592382199","data":{"timestamp":" 947592382199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592383326","data":{"timestamp":" 947592383324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINANE"," userResponse":" MINANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592384838","data":{"timestamp":" 947592384837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MYEMBAMBA"," userResponse":" MYEMBAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592385982","data":{"timestamp":" 947592385981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo hii Anansi Buibui ana miguu minane myembamba sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592388109","data":{"timestamp":" 947592388108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592389059","data":{"timestamp":" 947592389058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592389811","data":{"timestamp":" 947592389810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592390922","data":{"timestamp":" 947592390921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUPATA"," userResponse":" HAKUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592391693","data":{"timestamp":" 947592391693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592392512","data":{"timestamp":" 947592392512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592395306","data":{"timestamp":" 947592395303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592395382","data":{"timestamp":" 947592395382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOCHOTE"," userResponse":" CHOCHOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592442436","data":{"timestamp":" 947592442435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" f79f18a6-6949-42ef-b3b2-7cf3d3c40ad6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592458084","data":{"timestamp":" 947592458083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592458720","data":{"timestamp":" 947592458719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592458974","data":{"timestamp":" 947592458974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592459539","data":{"timestamp":" 947592459538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592460698","data":{"timestamp":" 947592460698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592461467","data":{"timestamp":" 947592461466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592462890","data":{"timestamp":" 947592462890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592463792","data":{"timestamp":" 947592463791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592464430","data":{"timestamp":" 947592464430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592465375","data":{"timestamp":" 947592465374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592466030","data":{"timestamp":" 947592466029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592468464","data":{"timestamp":" 947592468463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592468720","data":{"timestamp":" 947592468720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592469655","data":{"timestamp":" 947592469654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592470543","data":{"timestamp":" 947592470542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592471391","data":{"timestamp":" 947592471390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPISHI"," userResponse":" MPISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592472298","data":{"timestamp":" 947592472297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mke wa Anansi alikuwa mpishi mzuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592475053","data":{"timestamp":" 947592475053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592475489","data":{"timestamp":" 947592475489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592476201","data":{"timestamp":" 947592476200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592477262","data":{"timestamp":" 947592477261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592478197","data":{"timestamp":" 947592478197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592479023","data":{"timestamp":" 947592479022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONJA"," userResponse":" KUONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592479973","data":{"timestamp":" 947592479972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592481595","data":{"timestamp":" 947592481594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOPIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592481805","data":{"timestamp":" 947592481804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592482671","data":{"timestamp":" 947592482670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592483386","data":{"timestamp":" 947592483385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592483699","data":{"timestamp":" 947592483698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592484584","data":{"timestamp":" 947592484584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592485658","data":{"timestamp":" 947592485657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kila mara Anansi alipenda kuonja vyakula vilivyopikwa na wanawake wengine wa pale kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592488735","data":{"timestamp":" 947592488734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592489356","data":{"timestamp":" 947592489356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592490467","data":{"timestamp":" 947592490466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592491618","data":{"timestamp":" 947592491618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPITA"," userResponse":" ALIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592491972","data":{"timestamp":" 947592491971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592492853","data":{"timestamp":" 947592492852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592494090","data":{"timestamp":" 947592494090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" RAFIKIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592494930","data":{"timestamp":" 947592494929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Anansi alipita kwa Sungura rafikiye mpendwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPENDWA"," userResponse":" MPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592497595","data":{"timestamp":" 947592497594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592498495","data":{"timestamp":" 947592498495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592499079","data":{"timestamp":" 947592499078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592499328","data":{"timestamp":" 947592499327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592500059","data":{"timestamp":" 947592500058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592500876","data":{"timestamp":" 947592500876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592503544","data":{"timestamp":" 947592503544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592504545","data":{"timestamp":" 947592504544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592505024","data":{"timestamp":" 947592505023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592505295","data":{"timestamp":" 947592505294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592506087","data":{"timestamp":" 947592506087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592507391","data":{"timestamp":" 947592507391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592507730","data":{"timestamp":" 947592507730"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592508195","data":{"timestamp":" 947592508195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592508287","data":{"timestamp":" 947592508286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592568265","data":{"timestamp":" 947592568264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 4d256b7d-db20-440d-8077-978f502054d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Anansi anapenda mboga za majani akasema kwa msisimuko kuna mboga za majani kwenye chungu chako."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947592578894","data":{"timestamp":" 947592578894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_140519"," gameId":" 1782b34c-347d-4f56-b0ca-857b7facef17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}